<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>flix on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/flix/</link>
    <description>Recent content in flix on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/flix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flix - Catalunya</title>
      <link>/2017-08-23-catalunya-flix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2017-08-23-catalunya-flix/</guid>
      <description>Can&amp;rsquo;t believe I am writing this with only 5 days of our 6 weeks left, where has the time gone, it just disappears when you are enjoying yourself.&#xA;{{ more }}&#xA;Punta De láguila 8th Aug&#xA;Flo got a walking map of the area around Asco from the tourist office. One of the walks starting at the Hermita Santa Paulina appealed to us both, so we download the gpx file to wikiloc and off we went.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Margalef </title>
      <link>/2017-07-31-margalef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2017-07-31-margalef/</guid>
      <description>We went for a walk to the Hermita but not before finding a bar for a coffee.&#xA;Some View&#xA;{{ more }}&#xA;The walk up to the Hermita was fairly easy, with exceptional views of the surrounding area although it was hot their was a nice cooling breeze. The walk back down was much easier as we took the road.&#xA;The Hermita&#xA;This area is known for it climbing and there where two groups doing there thing on the rocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Cycle in Taragona</title>
      <link>/2017-07-17-first-cycle-in-taragona/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2017-07-17-first-cycle-in-taragona/</guid>
      <description>A bit windy today but decided to take the plunge and brave the C-12 to Flix wasn&amp;rsquo;t too bad.&#xA;Our First Passage On A Barca&#xA;{{ more }}&#xA;I decided on a short run due to the wind and not knowing the roads , fairly easy spin with some very poor road surface, which was made up for by a newly resurfaced section on a fast twisty decent.&#xA;On a whim I turned on to the back road into Flix and at the top of a steep hill found Flo photographing a sign, we both continued on to Flix only to find our route blocked by the river, luckily for us there was a free ferry across the river although it was one of the strangest I have come across.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
