<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Holiday on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/holiday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Holiday on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/holiday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Last Day</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-15-achill-sound-last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-15-achill-sound-last-day/</guid>
      <description>Drove back home from Achill today but not before one last coffee in the Village Bakery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Friday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-14-achill-sound-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-14-achill-sound-friday/</guid>
      <description>Castlebar for coffee today just for a change of scenery Cafe Rua great spot nice coffee and chocolate cake, walked round the town and Flo debated buying a pair of boots but decided against
Westport was the next port of call and the West Bar for Lunch, unfortunatly Flo&amp;rsquo;s back was giving her a lot of trouble so it was a quick walk round town and back to the cottage to pack fro home on Sat</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Thursday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-13-achill-sound-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-13-achill-sound-thursday/</guid>
      <description>Coffee and Grocery Shopping this morning then back home for Lunch. Flo fancied going to one of the television masts and view points but as soon as we left the house the mist came down and the wind got even stronger. When we got there, there where some guys painting the mast could not believe anyone would work in such poor and dangerous conditions
Having seen the waves from the mountain we decided to have a closer look, the wind was wild and the mist very low but the beach was great, and the wind surfers worth watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Wednesday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-12-achill-sound-wednesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-12-achill-sound-wednesday/</guid>
      <description>Had a lazy morning round the Cottage and then went to the Village Bakery for our usall coffee, and then a drive around the Atlantic Drive fab sceenery.
Early evening and we went to Calveys for a meal, it was great, good food and wine, and the service was very good as well a really nice spot and I think we would come back here for a meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-11-achill-sound-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-11-achill-sound-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>The drive to Keem Beach was very hilly with great scenery, the beach it&amp;rsquo;s self was fantastic got some good shots of Lotti and flo. Luckily we had finished when a Coach load of tourists arrived so it was time to leave.
Drove round to the abandoned Village and then more Coffee where we watched some poor unfortunates trying to break into their car.
We walked to Alices Bar for some food and meet some Canadians from Novia Socia looking for directions, naturally we got soaked both ways heavy rain and strong winds but still quit mild.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Monday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-10-achill-sound-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-10-achill-sound-monday/</guid>
      <description>Need some supplies and coffee, The Village Bakery provided the first of many coffee stops and I wanted a look round the hardware store which turned out to be what we expected a mix of the old and new.
We drove to Newport and around Furnace lake and back to Achill for lunch. I thought we could walk lotti round the shore and back up a river on to the road but the beginning of the river proved illusive so we gave up and took Lotti back the way we came, leaving her in the house we walked back along the road to the top of the river and then followed it to the sea, not an easy walk good job we left Lotti home and of course the rain returned and we got soaked but it was good fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Sunday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-09-achill-sound-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-09-achill-sound-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Walked into town this morning to get the papers, naturaly the rainn started on the way home so we stopped in the pub for a coffee even lotti was allowed in. A quick drive round the NE side of the Island this evening just foe a quick look and the into Alice&amp;rsquo;s for a pint</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Saturday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-08-achill-sound-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-09-08-achill-sound-saturday/</guid>
      <description>After a lovely dive we arrive in Achill Sound and the cottage looks good but the weather not so much.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>