<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>holiday on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/holiday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in holiday on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/holiday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lough Money and Whiterock</title>
      <link>/2014-09-11-lough-money-and-whiterock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-09-11-lough-money-and-whiterock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2014/2014-09-11-lough-money-and-whiterock.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Full Day of our Holiday</title>
      <link>/2014-09-03-last-full-day-of-our-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-09-03-last-full-day-of-our-holiday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last day of our holidays so I added a couple of loops together and ended up with a decent run once again it was very warm and sunny.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flo Cycle and Coffee in Monserrat</title>
      <link>/2014-09-02-flo-cycle-and-coffee-in-monserrat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-09-02-flo-cycle-and-coffee-in-monserrat/</guid>
      <description>Out for a spin with Flo again today. Trying to find the road from Turis to Chiva was like looking for a needle in a haystack, finaly Flo found it and we had shorter reverse of Sundays run, with Coffee in Monserrat.
Spent the evening watching a distant thunder storm from the pool, no sound just the light show. Today&amp;rsquo;s route was Altury, Turis, Godelleta, Monserrat, Montroy, Real and Turis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Cycle let down by poor Maps and Signs</title>
      <link>/2014-09-01-long-cycle-let-down-by-poor-maps-and-signs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-09-01-long-cycle-let-down-by-poor-maps-and-signs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2014/2014-09-01-long-cycle-let-down-by-poor-maps-and-signs.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;I should have been here!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycle and Jazz in the Amfiteatre</title>
      <link>/2014-08-31-cycle-and-jazz-in-the-amfiteatre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-31-cycle-and-jazz-in-the-amfiteatre/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2014/2014-08-31-cycle-and-jazz-in-the-amfiteatre.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Vuelta Albarcete</title>
      <link>/2014-08-30-la-vuelta-albarcete/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-30-la-vuelta-albarcete/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }} We left Altury around 10:00 and arrived in Albarcete about 13:00, we took a longer route but it was worth it as the scenery was lovely and once again the roads dead quite.
We drove into the centre of Albarcete and parked in an underground car park about 500mts from the stage finish.
After getting orientated we bought some Vuelta goodies and went to get something to eat in a nearby bar, we took up position on the 50 meter line and watched the race unfold on the big screen while collecting loads of pruck from the publicity caravan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sedajazz</title>
      <link>/2014-08-29-sedajazz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-29-sedajazz/</guid>
      <description>The plan to day is to drop Mairead off at Valencia Airport, and for us to go shopping in the big supper market in Bonaire. {{ more }}
This evening we went to the first night of the Jazz Festival in Turis where we saw Sedajazz a good band in novel surroundings for us any way, outside, night time, warm and dry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paddy Fields in Valencia</title>
      <link>/2014-08-28-paddy-fields-in-valencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-28-paddy-fields-in-valencia/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}
Got up early this morning to cycle in the cooler morning air, very over cast actually looked like it would rain. Change of direction went Turis Altury Alborache Dos Aguas Truis the descents where better this direction.
Got back early and while the others went out I enjoyed a leisurely shower.
Early evening and we went to the paddy fields for Paella in Raco de les Eres then back to La Font for our desert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dos Aguas and Mason Bar</title>
      <link>/2014-08-27-dos-aguas-and-mason-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-27-dos-aguas-and-mason-bar/</guid>
      <description>Flo and I cycled to Dos Aguis Macastre Alberache Turis with a refuelling stop in Macastre, Flo not dealing well with the heat once again it was 41c at the top of the climbs. The BB started to get noisy again so I stripped it down and gave it a through cleaning . {{ more }}
Tonight we went to Monserat for food and it was good except way too warm in the Mason bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Torrent, Bonaire and La Font</title>
      <link>/2014-08-26-torrent-bonaire-and-la-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-26-torrent-bonaire-and-la-font/</guid>
      <description>Banking and Shopping in Torrent and Bonaire with a visit to the train station to see about going into Valencia but we are not sure if we could cope in the heat.
{{ more }}
La Font for our evening meal, arrived too early so where forced to have a drink outside while we waited for the restaurant to open. The meal was lovely and great value at €80 for 3 three course meals and a bottle of wine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Bearings</title>
      <link>/2014-08-25-searching-for-bearings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-25-searching-for-bearings/</guid>
      <description>After much messing around and the use of a translator we could only get an 10m Allen key and no bearings. We rang John back in Cork to see if he could get bearings brought by one of his fiends. However when I got home and removed the cranks the bearing where fine. so I rebuild and the noise was gone. {{ more }}
I went for a test ride and the bike was fine, no creaking, but I have never experienced wind like it unbelievably hot very strange for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost in 43c Heat</title>
      <link>/2014-08-24-lost-in-43c-heat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-24-lost-in-43c-heat/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s route didn&amp;rsquo;t go as planned got lost all most as soon as we left Altury, and we ended up riding on the CV50 much more than I wanted to.
{{ more }}
After buying a map in L&amp;rsquo;Alcudia we were able to pick our way slightly better, although we still had one major detour on the way to Picasent, once we got to Picasent we picked up the road to Turis and back to Altury.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our First day in Turis</title>
      <link>/2014-08-23-our-first-day-in-turis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-23-our-first-day-in-turis/</guid>
      <description>After last nights drinking and eating I managed to sleep to 09:00, so after breakfast I built up my bike and adjusted Flo&amp;rsquo;s so they would be ready for tomorrow.
{{ more }}
I helped Mairead and Flo finish cleaning the pool , and then we went to Turis for a coffee and to buy food for tomorrow. Back home and I showered an relaxed until we go for a walk later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arriving in Turis</title>
      <link>/2014-08-22-arriving-in-turis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014-08-22-arriving-in-turis/</guid>
      <description>Arrived at the airport with sufficient time for an easy check in although the place was busier than we expected due probably to it being a bank holiday, any all went smoothly and we collect luggage and hire car with minimal fuss and we where on our way.
{{ more }}
Our first port of call was Valencia airport to pick up Mairead, then Turis to the shops for some necessary food and beer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day of the Disappearing Cake</title>
      <link>/2013-09-24-the-day-of-the-disappearing-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013-09-24-the-day-of-the-disappearing-cake/</guid>
      <description>Arrived in Achill around 16:00 minus a cake&amp;hellip;.
{{ more }}
The drive was fairly uneventful but we do need to find a better coffee stop on the way as Fivemile town isn&amp;rsquo;t up to scratch. Cycling and coffee tomorrow WP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Last Day</title>
      <link>/2012-09-15-achill-sound-last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-09-15-achill-sound-last-day/</guid>
      <description>Drove back home from Achill today but not before one last coffee in the Village Bakery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Friday</title>
      <link>/2012-09-14-achill-sound-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-09-14-achill-sound-friday/</guid>
      <description>Castlebar for coffee today just for a change of scenery Cafe Rua great spot nice coffee and chocolate cake, walked round the town and Flo debated buying a pair of boots but decided against
Westport was the next port of call and the West Bar for Lunch, unfortunatly Flo&amp;rsquo;s back was giving her a lot of trouble so it was a quick walk round town and back to the cottage to pack fro home on Sat</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Thursday</title>
      <link>/2012-09-13-achill-sound-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-09-13-achill-sound-thursday/</guid>
      <description>Coffee and Grocery Shopping this morning then back home for Lunch. Flo fancied going to one of the television masts and view points but as soon as we left the house the mist came down and the wind got even stronger. When we got there, there where some guys painting the mast could not believe anyone would work in such poor and dangerous conditions
Having seen the waves from the mountain we decided to have a closer look, the wind was wild and the mist very low but the beach was great, and the wind surfers worth watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Wednesday</title>
      <link>/2012-09-12-achill-sound-wednesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-09-12-achill-sound-wednesday/</guid>
      <description>Had a lazy morning round the Cottage and then went to the Village Bakery for our usall coffee, and then a drive around the Atlantic Drive fab sceenery.
Early evening and we went to Calveys for a meal, it was great, good food and wine, and the service was very good as well a really nice spot and I think we would come back here for a meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Tuesday</title>
      <link>/2012-09-11-achill-sound-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-09-11-achill-sound-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>The drive to Keem Beach was very hilly with great scenery, the beach it&amp;rsquo;s self was fantastic got some good shots of Lotti and flo. Luckily we had finished when a Coach load of tourists arrived so it was time to leave.
Drove round to the abandoned Village and then more Coffee where we watched some poor unfortunates trying to break into their car.
We walked to Alices Bar for some food and meet some Canadians from Novia Socia looking for directions, naturally we got soaked both ways heavy rain and strong winds but still quit mild.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Monday</title>
      <link>/2012-09-10-achill-sound-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-09-10-achill-sound-monday/</guid>
      <description>Need some supplies and coffee, The Village Bakery provided the first of many coffee stops and I wanted a look round the hardware store which turned out to be what we expected a mix of the old and new.
We drove to Newport and around Furnace lake and back to Achill for lunch. I thought we could walk lotti round the shore and back up a river on to the road but the beginning of the river proved illusive so we gave up and took Lotti back the way we came, leaving her in the house we walked back along the road to the top of the river and then followed it to the sea, not an easy walk good job we left Lotti home and of course the rain returned and we got soaked but it was good fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Sunday</title>
      <link>/2012-09-09-achill-sound-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-09-09-achill-sound-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Walked into town this morning to get the papers, naturaly the rainn started on the way home so we stopped in the pub for a coffee even lotti was allowed in. A quick drive round the NE side of the Island this evening just foe a quick look and the into Alice&amp;rsquo;s for a pint</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achill Sound Saturday</title>
      <link>/2012-09-08-achill-sound-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-09-08-achill-sound-saturday/</guid>
      <description>After a lovely dive we arrive in Achill Sound and the cottage looks good but the weather not so much.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
