<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>diet on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/diet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in diet on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/diet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fast Diet Quick Update</title>
      <link>/2013-03-09-fast-diet-quick-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-03-09-fast-diet-quick-update/</guid>
      <description>No cycling this week due to my crash last weekend, but I noticed no weakness after fasting so it would seem that it is a result of the exercise.
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Diet One Month On</title>
      <link>/2013-02-28-fast-diet-one-month-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-02-28-fast-diet-one-month-on/</guid>
      <description>One month and nine fast days later it looks like we will continue with the diet for the far see able future.
{{ more }} I have lost 8lbs so far without too much trouble. The fasting days have become easier and drinking hot water when hungry helps , tea and coffee in moderation.
Cycling is better done on fast days and recovering or a light ride the next day, I have felt slightly week the day after a fast and exercise I need to find out if this is due to the fast or the exercise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fast Diet</title>
      <link>/2013-02-05-the-fast-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-02-05-the-fast-diet/</guid>
      <description>On Friday 1st we started the Fast Diet (worst name ever) which involves fasting for two days a week.
The basics of the diet are that for two days a week you limit your calorie intake to 600 cals, split between breakfast and dinner, you can drink as much calorie free drink as you want. We chose Mon and Fri to start as we where travelling on these days and food was not readily available, we plan to fast on Mon and Thur from now on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22lbs Off</title>
      <link>/2011-12-17-22lbs-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 10:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-12-17-22lbs-off/</guid>
      <description>Getting harder now Christmas is fast approaching, but holding steady at 11st 10lbs. Hard to get out on the bike as the weather has turned nasty. Heavy Showers and icy roads today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 lbs lost</title>
      <link>/2011-11-17-14-lbs-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 22:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-11-17-14-lbs-lost/</guid>
      <description>Half way there!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Day of the Diet</title>
      <link>/2011-10-03-first-day-of-the-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 10:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-10-03-first-day-of-the-diet/</guid>
      <description>13 stone 4 pounds No chocolate.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
