<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>garden on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/garden/</link>
    <description>Recent content in garden on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 19:56:12 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/garden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Another Month Rolls By</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2021-10-31-another-month-rolls-by/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 19:56:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2021-10-31-another-month-rolls-by/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After much procrastinating we made a start to the fire, Built up the back and sides with some small bricks then we tiled the hearth with black tiles. We ran out of time to do the surround, that will have to wait for another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next project is to fit a Pellet Stove which we bought from Leroy Merlin, easy to fit got it up and running quickly. However when the wind blows it causes major problems as the stove blows back and fills the house with smoke, as a best solution we moved the flue away from the wall we may need to raise it above the roof.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bought a Tilt 900 from Decathlon same as Flo&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Borrowed a Rotavator from C&amp;amp;A went over it a couple of times, going to leave it a couple of days and I will do it again, so now the garden is ready for planting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s All About the Garden</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2021-02-28-its-all-about-the-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2021-02-28-its-all-about-the-garden/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We decided to concentrate on the Kitchen Garden and we are halfway through filling our 3rd skip, but we had to take a break bolloxed, 23c and heavy work but the end is near, and the garden is clear of all rubbish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://keithmillar.github.io/images/2021/2021-02-28-its-all-about-the-garden.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Irrigation system up and running&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Irrigation system up and running&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-08-22-garden-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 18:43:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-08-22-garden-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://keithmillar.github.io/images/2019/2019-08-22-garden-upgrade-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Garden&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready for the Fun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well it took a bit longer than we thought but we finally got the bottom half of the garden upgraded with new Flower beds, and we replace the moss and grass with membrane and stones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sparrowhawk</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2014-05-20-sparrowhawk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2014-05-20-sparrowhawk/</guid>
      <description>Manic scenes in the garden, birds going crazy, then I understood why. {{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tree lopping and another Barbie</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-07-21-tree-lopping-and-another-barbie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-07-21-tree-lopping-and-another-barbie/</guid>
      <description>After flo returned from Dublin I Started to cut down the trees in the school.
{{ more }}
Naturally the school never maintain any thing so it is up to us to cut the trees which are putting the garden into shade in the early afternoon, 3 hours later we had just about finished but decided to wait until tomorrow afternoon so we could see if any more need cutting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-04-29-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 08:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-04-29-easter/</guid>
      <description>With the weather remaining excellent for this time of year, we have got lots of things done. Thanks to Tim who supplied some manure , we where able to plant our Veg garden Broccoli, Carrots, Sweet Pea, Strawberries and Corvettes.
Easter Tue and it was the Club Easter Ramble to Newcastle, an over cast cool windy day and busy roads, 12 of us did the ride with lunch in Mauds. This was my second 100 miler this month, I thing the fact that the club where all in Mallorca doing big miles helped with the motivation and once again April is my highest mileage month so far.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
