<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>walking on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/walking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in walking on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/walking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tollymore</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-07-11-tollymore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-07-11-tollymore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://keithmillar.github.io/images/2019/2019-07-11-tollymore-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Silent Valley&#34; /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silent Valley&lt;/strong&gt;
Spent the 12th weekend in Tollymore Forest Park with the Lyttles. Saturday we all cycled by Spelga, Silent Valley and into Newcastle stopping at the Carrick Cottage Cafe for the necessary sustenance, and if that wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough ice cream in Newcastle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCool Hikers</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-10-02-mccool-hikers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-10-02-mccool-hikers/</guid>
      <description>McCool Hikers Day 1 After meeting G&amp;amp;H on Friday evening we stayed with Judi and did some catching up.
Sat morning was dull windy and very mild 18c at 07:30, after breakfast we headed into Phoenix park heavy traffic and going the wrong way meant we where late and missed the group arrival, however after much searching we gave up and went and watched the start of the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitterly Cold Easter</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-04-03-bitterly-cold-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-04-03-bitterly-cold-easter/</guid>
      <description>March was the coldest since 1963 with an average temp of 3c Easter wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking to be any warmer.
{{ more }}
Tullynagardy Rd Walk
On Easter Monday Flo and I decided to brave the bitterly cold wind and go for a walk, so we went Crawfordsburn Rd Tullynagardy Rd Ballybarnes Rd Green Mile Clandyboye Leadmines Quarry Rd home.
Great walk but my arm did give me some pain.
On Tuesday Flo cycled while suffered on the Turbo, later we went to Muffler for coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delamont</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-11-11-delamont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-11-11-delamont/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundy Trail Parkway</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-09-22-fundy-trail-parkway/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 15:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-09-22-fundy-trail-parkway/</guid>
      <description>Beavers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Andrews</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-09-19-st-andrews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-09-19-st-andrews/</guid>
      <description>Kingsbrae gardens was the first stop to day A nice meal and then a walk round the gardens, some interesting sculptures to look at.
Then we drive down to the car park and followed the walking trail and managed 4 miles along the shore and back via the forest trails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lepreau Falls New River Beach</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-09-18-lepreau-falls-new-river-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 17:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-09-18-lepreau-falls-new-river-beach/</guid>
      <description>The Falls
A quick visit to the falls and then on to New River Beach. A 3 mile walk along the shore and back through the trees, Followed a long distance swimmer for some of the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia National Park</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-09-12-acadia-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 06:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-09-12-acadia-national-park/</guid>
      <description>First we went to Thunder Hole then a 4 mile walk in ANC. Lovely warm day blue sky, very hard walking nearly vertical in places more of a scramble. Passed an elderly couple who were having a hard time, little did they know worse was to come. When we returned to the car park we spoke to the range and informed her about them just in case they got into difficulty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omaha Beach Wexford</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-07-12-omaha-beach-wexford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 19:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2011-07-12-omaha-beach-wexford/</guid>
      <description>Omaha Beach
Flo &amp;amp; Kath</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Walk</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-12-21-snow-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 22:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-12-21-snow-walk/</guid>
      <description>With the tempature hovering around -6 we decided to go for a Moonlight walk from Ards Shopping Center to Scrabo and then around the Golf course and in Killynether then returning to the car.
Marty &amp;amp; FLo
Marty &amp;amp; Flo with Flash
Scrabo Tower
Ards by Moonlight
Mysterious Tracks in the Snow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycling &amp; Walking in the Mournes</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-03-27-cycling-walking-in-themournes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-03-27-cycling-walking-in-themournes/</guid>
      <description>Marty and myself set off from Newtownards at 7:30 and cycled to Meelmore Lodge about 40 miles , where we meet up with Flo. After a quick change of clothing it was off up the trassey track to the hare&amp;rsquo;s gap where we regrouped, and following the Brandy Pad we walked round Slieve Commedagh. Turning left we headed to the mourne wall and the valley between Donard and Commedagh. We then followed th Mourne Wall over Commedagh and Back to the Hare&amp;rsquo;s gap and finaly back to Meelmore Lodge, covering about 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-01-31-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-01-31-january/</guid>
      <description>Not much happening at this time of year, so the start of the month was fairly quite. However we had a weekend away planned for the very end of the month in Co Roscommon.
Lough Key
We drove down to Ballghadereen Co Roscommon on Friday night, the drive to Enniskillen was woeful due to road works but when we crosssed the border it turned into a lovely bright moon lite night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas &amp; New Year</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-12-31-christmas-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-12-31-christmas-new-year/</guid>
      <description>Garth arrived on 18th at 05:30 and with him came the first snow of the year and freezing temperatures. After Breakfast in the travelodge it was of to Maria&amp;rsquo;s to get the dart into Dublin.
Off the DART and a cold busy Dublin awaited us. A quick walk around the city centre with a visit to HMV and the Post Office on O&amp;rsquo;Connell Street, which was pretty much the original building.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>