<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dining on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/dining/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dining on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/dining/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>John &amp; Fiona</title>
      <link>/2013-11-30-john-fiona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013-11-30-john-fiona/</guid>
      <description>Finally after much procrastinating we got round to having John and Fiona over for a meal.
{{ more }}
Flo worked hard to produce a great spread of food, which was devoured along with several bottles of wine.
It was nice to be able to return the compliment for the Christmas dinners we have enjoyed at their house.
It was good catching up and finding out what Mark and Lisa where doing, both seem well on the way to careers of their own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Barbie in Years</title>
      <link>/2013-07-19-first-barbie-in-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013-07-19-first-barbie-in-years/</guid>
      <description>After returning from Wexford and the weather is still fantastic we could only do one thing!
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flo&#39;s week off comes to an end</title>
      <link>/2013-03-24-flos-week-off-comes-to-an-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013-03-24-flos-week-off-comes-to-an-end/</guid>
      <description>We rounded off a nice week off with a bitterly cold walk down the flood gates and then a few pints and some food in Roma&amp;rsquo;s.
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Anniversary</title>
      <link>/2013-02-27-wedding-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013-02-27-wedding-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Twenty years, doesn&amp;rsquo;t time fly and so far so good. May and Carole gave us a voucher at Christmas for Daft Eddys so it only seemed right that we use it towards our anniversary celebrations. Lots of new staff so we where a bit concerned incase the food wasn&amp;rsquo;t up to the usual standard, but it was even better.
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Day</title>
      <link>/2012-12-25-christmas-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-12-25-christmas-day/</guid>
      <description>Lotti helping with the Presents
{{ more }}
Christmas Dinner
Dessert
Our Hosts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flo&#39;s week off</title>
      <link>/2012-11-19-flos-week-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-11-19-flos-week-off/</guid>
      <description>After Flo had to cancle her second weeks holiday when she hurt her back she booked this week off. Monday and we went to the new James Bond film Skyfall which was very good and we got the cinema almost to our selves.
{{ more }}
Wednesday we both went out on our bikes and I meet up with Flo in Bowbell and we came back with the club. Thursday we went into Belfast for lunch and a look around town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karen&#39;s Visit</title>
      <link>/2012-10-27-karens-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-10-27-karens-visit/</guid>
      <description>Did Harry&amp;rsquo;s run this morning on the Fixie and then went to Decathlon with Flo and Karen. Spent a fortune but I did get a nice coat.
{{ more }}
Colin and bev had their Haloween party on Saturday night, the crac was mighty and it was good to catch up with everyone and to see the children growing up.
Sunday was a more relaxed day, went to Castle Espie for morning coffee and read the paper, the in the evening we went to the Parlour for tea and a few pints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen and Titanic</title>
      <link>/2012-10-13-zen-and-titanic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-10-13-zen-and-titanic/</guid>
      <description>Frank and Kath spent the weekend with us and on Sat night we went to Zen for a meal, as to be expected it was very nice great atmosphere.
{{ more }}
Sunday and we went to the new titanic expo in Belfast, very well done for a change it looks like we have got something right although I suspect our politicians had little to do with it. To finish the day off we had Afternoon Tea and very nice it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flo&#39;s Birthday</title>
      <link>/2012-10-05-flos-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-10-05-flos-birthday/</guid>
      <description>This evening turned out to be quite busy, first I had an interview with Tesco in Newtownards and then more importantly Flo&amp;rsquo;s Birthday dinner at Daft Eddys.
The interview seemed to go well even though I had to wait for one of the interviewers. Needless to say I was declined a couple of weeks later.
The weather cleared up a little bit when we got to Daft Eddys and was very calm with a lovely sunset over the bay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big 50</title>
      <link>/2012-07-06-the-big-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-07-06-the-big-50/</guid>
      <description>Well to day finally came, never really thought it would. Woke up an Flo had lots of cards and presents for me to open, but the special one was my new Focus Cayo fortunately it was too wet to go out on it.
Using the old reliable Cannondale I went for coffee in Bowbells and got soaked on the way there. Friday evening We meet up with the Perrys and McCoshes in Daft Eddys for a meal and some crac, we had a great night and the children where very well behaved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Down GP and Daft Eddys</title>
      <link>/2012-05-26-west-down-gp-and-daft-eddys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-05-26-west-down-gp-and-daft-eddys/</guid>
      <description>West Down GP was run off on a lovely sunny day with a brutal wind which once again put a damper on the racing. A bunch speint it was with a down hill and tail wind assisted finish at over 40 mph I decided to let this one pass
On Sunday Flo and I went out for a spin to Daft Eddys, it was a lovely day but Flo was a bit sick so we had to cut the run short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix GP Wedding Anniversary</title>
      <link>/2012-02-27-phoenix-gp-wedding-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-02-27-phoenix-gp-wedding-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>First race of the year, Phoenix GP At Nutts Corner all went very well felt good and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t tested at all until the end tuff drag up to the finish managed to hang on for 8th place. Not a hard course just hope I can continue in the same vain in the coming races. Great day for the club as the two Noels took first and second in the over 50&amp;rsquo;s race while Matty won the A3 race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bokhara</title>
      <link>/2012-02-20-bokhara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-02-20-bokhara/</guid>
      <description>Had a lovely Meal in the Bokhara with Flo the went to the club rooms and collected my 2012 Licence. Next Tim&amp;rsquo;s place for a Coastal Challenge meeting, good meeting lots talked about and some good ideas about this years event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dree Hill &amp; Roma&#39;s</title>
      <link>/2012-01-23-dree-hill-and-romas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012-01-23-dree-hill-and-romas/</guid>
      <description>Headed over to Dromara and on over Dree Hill today, not sure it was one of my better ideas. Dree Hill was as hard as usual I was even chased up by a hedge cutter, but we got there in the end, alough I don&amp;rsquo;t think I had enough to eat and I ran out of energy on the way home, a hard day as it was a head wind out and quite cold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen</title>
      <link>/2011-08-06-zen-06-08-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 23:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2011-08-06-zen-06-08-11/</guid>
      <description>Flo &amp;amp; Flo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Souffle</title>
      <link>/2011-07-10-souffle-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 22:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2011-07-10-souffle-2/</guid>
      <description>Souffle</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
