<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cycling on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/cycling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cycling on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:27:04 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/cycling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>La Vuelta Cheste</title>
      <link>/2023-09-01-la-vuelta-cheste/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:27:04 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/2023-09-01-la-vuelta-cheste/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2023/2023-09-01-la-vuelta-break-cheste.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The break passing through Cheste&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The break passing through Cheste&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XI Cycloturista March Avapace</title>
      <link>/2023-06-11-xi-cycloturista-march-avapace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2023-06-11-xi-cycloturista-march-avapace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2023/2023-06-11-xi-cycloturista-march-avapace-5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;XI Cycloturista March Avapace&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;XI Cycloturista March Avapace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V Marcha Ciclodeportiva De Tous</title>
      <link>/2022-10-16-v-marcha-ciclodeportiva-de-tous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2022-10-16-v-marcha-ciclodeportiva-de-tous/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2022/2022-10-16-v-marcha-ciclodeportiva-de-tous.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Trying to cross the Dam since 1 Sept 2014 today was the day.&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trying to cross the Dam since 1 Sept 2014 today was the day.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garth&#39;s Visit</title>
      <link>/2022-06-17-garth-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2022-06-17-garth-visit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Due to the greed of airlines, airports etc Garth&amp;rsquo;s flight to Montreal
was cancelled, luckily he was able to get it rebooked for the next day and Helena got his return extended by one day. One day late but on time Garth finally arrived in Valencia. We took him to Bonaire for lunch then home to build his bike.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X Marcha Cicloturista Avapace</title>
      <link>/2022-06-12-x-marcha-cicloturista-avapace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 19:36:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/2022-06-12-x-marcha-cicloturista-avapace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2022/2022-06-12-x-marcha-cicloturista-avapace-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Flo ready for the Off&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flo ready for the Off&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dromara Destroyers</title>
      <link>/2021-07-26-dromara-destroyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 16:42:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/2021-07-26-dromara-destroyers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2021/2021-07-26-dromara-destroyers.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Marty and Colin&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marty and Colin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailer Trash</title>
      <link>/2020-08-03-trailer-trash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:31:07 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/2020-08-03-trailer-trash/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2020/2020-08-03-trailer-trash.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Trailer Trash&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailer Trash&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus Sold</title>
      <link>/2020-06-15-focus-sold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2020-06-15-focus-sold/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Marty was able to sell my Focus due to the demand for bikes because of Covid.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tollymore</title>
      <link>/2019-07-11-tollymore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2019-07-11-tollymore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2019/2019-07-11-tollymore-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Silent Valley&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silent Valley&lt;/strong&gt;
Spent the 12th weekend in Tollymore Forest Park with the Lyttles. Saturday we all cycled by Spelga, Silent Valley and into Newcastle stopping at the Carrick Cottage Cafe for the necessary sustenance, and if that wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough ice cream in Newcastle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volta a la Comunitat Valenciana</title>
      <link>/2019-02-08-volta-a-la-comunitat-valenciana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2019-02-08-volta-a-la-comunitat-valenciana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Up early for us and on the road for 09:00 to get to Pedralba for around 10:00 so we have time to find a good parking spot for Eddy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTT - XXIII Marcha Montroy</title>
      <link>/2019-01-27-btt-xxiii-marcha-montroy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2019-01-27-btt-xxiii-marcha-montroy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2019/2019-01-27-BTT-XXIII-Marcha-Montroy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BTT - XXIII Marcha Montroy&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;BTT - XXIII Marcha Montroy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Giant Terrago </title>
      <link>/2019-01-19-terrago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2019-01-19-terrago/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2019/2019-01-19-terrago.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Terrago&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;First Brief Spin On The Terrago&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ciclo Cross Ciudad de Xativa</title>
      <link>/2018-12-15-ciclo-cross-ciudad-de-xativa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-12-15-ciclo-cross-ciudad-de-xativa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2018/ciclo-cross-ciudad-de-xativa-aida-nuno.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Aida Nuño Race Winner and Current Spanish Champion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cycling with Garth</title>
      <link>/2018-09-08-cycling-with-garth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-09-08-cycling-with-garth/</guid>
      <description>Garth and I got some good bike rides in, as he was training for Kona in a few weeks time. One good long one and several shorter faster spins. Flo and Helena did a couple of rides as well one longer one with the quick chicks.
Didn&amp;rsquo;t do as much cycling as we hoped mainly because we returned home early because of lotti.
All our rides are on Garmin Connect etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRONMAN Mont-Tremblant</title>
      <link>/2018-08-17-ironman-mont-tremblant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-08-17-ironman-mont-tremblant/</guid>
      <description>Finally arrived in the race village after what seemed like an eternity travelling, and we where glad to have a rest. Garth was able to complete both the swim and the run and Helena stunned everyone by running the marathon in the hottest part of the day without a bother. {{ more }}
Garth Finishes The Swim
Helena Blasts the Run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garths Visit</title>
      <link>/2018-06-29-garths-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-06-29-garths-visit/</guid>
      <description>Picked up Garth from Dublin Airport early this morning as he is home for Carole&amp;rsquo;s Funeral
{{ more }}
Picked up the bike for Garth from Marty&amp;rsquo;s daughter and got it ready for a spin down the Pennisula tomorrow. Making the best of a bad thing Garth and I got some great bike rides in and the weather was out of this world.
Dree Hill
Dree Hill
Tue 3rd and Carole&amp;rsquo;s Funeral took place in Kirkwoods with the Cremation at Roselawn then La Mon for something to eat an nice day but very sad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpe d&#39;Huez</title>
      <link>/2018-06-08-alpe-d-huez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-06-08-alpe-d-huez/</guid>
      <description>Rode the mythical climb for the first time in 20yrs still hard. Discovered a great road back to Allemont fantastic views.
{{ more }}
Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez
Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez
Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez
Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Belgium</title>
      <link>/2018-04-17-more-belgium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-04-17-more-belgium/</guid>
      <description>Spending our last night in Holland, at an Aire on the Maas in a town called Blerick just beside Venlo. Interesting place overlooking a marina and major cargo port, watching barges being loaded and unload.
{{ more }}
Tuesday 17th
Arrived in Aywaille about 13:00 and got settled in the Campsite. Flo and I went and did some shopping then we collected Lotti and did more shopping. After tea we all walked into Aywaille and discovered the route for tomorrow race, so we returned to Eddy and planed our viewing of La Flèche Wallonne for both Wednesday and Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronde Van Vlaanderen</title>
      <link>/2018-04-01-ronde-van-vlaanderen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-04-01-ronde-van-vlaanderen/</guid>
      <description>Up early and a brisk walk to the train station for the first leg of our journey to Ode Kwaremont for the Tour of Flanders.
{{ more }}
All the trains where spot on and we arrived in Oudenaarde in good time for the bus to the course as we where waiting it poured down and looked set for the day but by the time we got to the Kwaremont it was dry for the rest of the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>La Vuelta a Espana</title>
      <link>/2017-08-22-la-vuelta-a-espana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2017-08-22-la-vuelta-a-espana/</guid>
      <description>La Vuelta a Espana 22 Aug Flo liked this shoe and sock combination
{{ more }}
The King of the hills was in a place called Belltall which was about 1 1/2 hours away. We arrived in plenty of time and after finding the top of the climb and a good place to park we where then able to have lunch in the town, in a Hostel Cal Feliute food was good and the service fast even though the place was packed due to the race passing through.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camping Rio Turia</title>
      <link>/2017-07-01-camping-rio-turia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2017-07-01-camping-rio-turia/</guid>
      <description>Camping Rio Turia Day 1 Arrived 15.00 to find the place quite busy and the pool filled as promised.
Set Blu up in a nice shaded site.
Rio Tura
{{ more }}
Enjoyed a beer over looking the river and watched a pair of Swallows feeding in the roof of the bar. Walked through Bugarra just to get our bearings for tomorrow.
Camping Rio Turia Day 2 Slept late and after breakfast we walked into Bugarra for a coffee and a toastada and then beer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girona Gran Fondo</title>
      <link>/2017-06-17-girona-gran-fondo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2017-06-17-girona-gran-fondo/</guid>
      <description>After what seemed like an eternity we arrived in Girona at 17:30 and lucky old Flo found a parking space on the river 1km from the event office, after picking up my race pack we meet with Marty for a beer and a quick catch-up we arranged to meet at 09:30 on the Pont de Pedra tomorrow.
Out in the Countryside {{ more }}
As normal when we meet the ride had changed from the shop run to a 50 mile spin to the beach with the Ards boys and some north downers .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class New Climb</title>
      <link>/2017-05-09-class-new-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2017-05-09-class-new-climb/</guid>
      <description>Found this road (vp-5051) last week after passing it quite a few times in the past, I new it was there I just didn&amp;rsquo;t know if it could be made part of a run.
{{ more }}
Looking at the map I realised it joined back onto the cv-580 Dos Aguas Alborache Rd , so I decided to give it a go.
A slightly narrow road but superb surface and views to die for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First trip to St Andrews</title>
      <link>/2016-07-03-first-trip-to-st-andrews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-07-03-first-trip-to-st-andrews/</guid>
      <description>Pre Challenge trip to St Andrews
{{ more }} Quick out and back spin with Garth to Cape Spencer, while Helena and Flo did the same route, another lovely morning, quite impressed with the Kona.
Then we drove down to Saint Andrews for G &amp;amp; H to have a meeting with Tressa, Flo and I wandered round the town sorting things for next week and the Challenge event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Village Spin</title>
      <link>/2016-06-30-french-village-spin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-06-30-french-village-spin/</guid>
      <description>Adjusted Helena&amp;rsquo;s bike and Garth and I parked in the Irving Station and we headed off on the roads around French Village.
The temperature increased up to 29c but the humidity was the real killer not very nice. At one point a guy on a motor bike complement us on our speed and cornering ability. Hard roads but a lovely place, would make a nice place to build if we decide to move here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee and Saddle Test</title>
      <link>/2016-03-26-coffee-and-saddle-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-03-26-coffee-and-saddle-test/</guid>
      <description>Flo Left 15 mins before me but I caught her too soon so we changed our coffee stop to El Dolcet in Montserrat. After the coffee we each headed off on own to finish the spin. This was the hottest day of our visit so far with the Garmin showing 31c , unfortunately the wind was savage but the down hill tail wind bits where brill. Flo done really well considering the wind and hills, following most of my route all but the cv-50.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gestalgar Bugarra Pedralba Spin</title>
      <link>/2016-03-01-gestalgar-bugarra-pedralba-spin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-03-01-gestalgar-bugarra-pedralba-spin/</guid>
      <description>Nice ride through Chiva to Gestalgar quite hilly through a forest to Gestalgar which is nestled in a valley right at the foot of some big mountians. The road was closed, luckly there was a nice dirversion to Bugarra which seemed to be more a collection of factories, Pedralba on the other hand looks like it would be worth a visit on foot.
Today was once again very windy and I ended up with a cross head wind all the way home, and the roads where draggy and wide open no shelter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murcia and Torrevieja</title>
      <link>/2016-01-31-murcia-and-torrevieja/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-01-31-murcia-and-torrevieja/</guid>
      <description>We spent a few day down in Torrevieja with Sam McMinn and then Gerry Kearney it meant we had to return to Turis and then go back down to Gerry&amp;rsquo;s but it was worth it as we got some great rides in, and I was able to take Flo and Gerry to the Airport.
{{ more }} Most of Sam runs went from Bar Studzs and involved the Amigos del Ciclismo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best laid plans … by Flo</title>
      <link>/2016-01-21-the-best-laid-plans-by-flo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-01-21-the-best-laid-plans-by-flo/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }} This morning Keith &amp;amp; myself set off to go to on our first joint cycle (apart from the transportation to Turis early on back in December – and that’s enough about that!!!) with a trip back to Tous.
Started off, having walked Lotti, with a beautiful blue sky, warm and little breeze at about 10:30am. Got to L’Alcudia and went off route (well, I did do it on the laptop without having been on the roads before !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam&#39;s Run</title>
      <link>/2015-07-05-sam-s-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2015-07-05-sam-s-run/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wexford &amp; La Ruta del Murrintowneo</title>
      <link>/2015-06-10-wexford/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2015-06-10-wexford/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}
Arrived around 19:30 as the traffic was fairly heavy, but it was a nice bright day for a change.
Thursday we awoke to no internet access and even the stable diet in Wexford does not have wifi, spent a nice day with Kath and Frank before they all head off to Italy.
Friday the wind and rain woke us so we moved our planed cycle to Saturday and headed into Wexford where Flo spent a small fortune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Italian Bike Ride Aborted</title>
      <link>/2015-05-03-big-italian-bike-ride-aborted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2015-05-03-big-italian-bike-ride-aborted/</guid>
      <description>Can&amp;rsquo;t think why I stayed in Bed today. {{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titanic Torr and March Roundup</title>
      <link>/2015-03-31-titanic-torr-and-march-roundup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2015-03-31-titanic-torr-and-march-roundup/</guid>
      <description>First nice day for a long time so we took Lotti to Ballywalter for a swim. Must be a year since we where last here. {{ more }}
After much deliberation Marty and I entered the Titanic Torr, having a good idea that we would do this ride I had done some good long rides, 90 plus miles so I was confident of doing the distance.
On The day the weather could not have been better light Northerly wind and clear blue skies, the route was good with many new roads especially at the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granite Challenge</title>
      <link>/2014-10-05-granite-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2014-10-05-granite-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Flo Celebrating her Birthday with a Handy Cycle.
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synapse</title>
      <link>/2014-10-04-synapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2014-10-04-synapse/</guid>
      <description>The latest addition.
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giro d&#39;Italia Stormont</title>
      <link>/2014-05-09-giro-d-italia-stormont/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2014-05-09-giro-d-italia-stormont/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Drive Route 1</title>
      <link>/2013-09-27-atlantic-drive-route-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-09-27-atlantic-drive-route-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Near perfect conditions for our bike ride today little wind and very warm. The ride turned out to be a lot easier than I thought.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Western Greenway</title>
      <link>/2013-09-25-great-western-greenway/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-09-25-great-western-greenway/</guid>
      <description>Fogy and damp this morning but no wind to speak of and quite warm, so a good day to tackle the Greenway.
{{ more }} We rode from Achill to Newport via the Great Western Greenway ,easy going with only one steep section at Mullranny. The most interesting part is from Achill to Mullranny, with some nice views of the loughs. From Mullranny to Newport is very flat open moorland not the best when the wind is blowing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marie Curie</title>
      <link>/2013-09-17-marie-curie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-09-17-marie-curie/</guid>
      <description>The weather forecast for Sunday was dire, rain and gale force winds. Flo had already decide to do the Marie Curie on Saturday and I didn&amp;rsquo;t fancy the Ards run on Sunday so the Marie Curie it was.
{{ more }}
Quite a few of the Club where going to Downpatrick so I joined them in Ards and we took the quite back roads to the start at Downpatrick race course, with Flo driving down and getting an early start on her own with the intention of me catching her later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cycle and a Barbie</title>
      <link>/2013-08-25-cycle-and-a-barbie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-08-25-cycle-and-a-barbie/</guid>
      <description>Went out this morning with the Sunday run another great day warm and sunny, this is becoming a really good summer.
{{ more }}
We even went as far as having another barbie this afternoon just because we could.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirkistown Final Round</title>
      <link>/2013-08-21-kirkistown-final-round/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-08-21-kirkistown-final-round/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ardill &amp; Patterson Club Championships</title>
      <link>/2013-08-07-ardill-and-patterson-club-championships/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-08-07-ardill-and-patterson-club-championships/</guid>
      <description>Almost perfect conditions tonight for the road race light winds warm and dry. This has to be one of the best marshalled club events I have ever been at thanks in part to the Peninsula Tri club.
{{ more }}
Numbers where down on the usual mob that descends on Kirkistown, probably because this was a road course with hills and sharp corners. There where 3 groups on the road Ladies &amp;amp; over 50s, over 40s and senior riders with each group riding to win a club jersey in their respective class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police And Fire Games - Crit</title>
      <link>/2013-08-05-police-and-fire-games-crit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-08-05-police-and-fire-games-crit/</guid>
      <description>To night could not have been more different than last Wednesday nights Time Trial, bright blue sky and light winds, ideal conditions for racing.
{{ more }}
Four races where on the cards, Woman and over 70s, over 50s, over 40s, and up to 39. We had two riders in the over 50s class John Hunter and Noel Boyce, Noel went on to win his third gold. Michael Mcmullan riding in the over 40s was riding well but was unfortunate to puncture and unable to finish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police And Fire Games -  Hill Climb</title>
      <link>/2013-07-31-police-and-fire-games-hill-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-07-31-police-and-fire-games-hill-climb/</guid>
      <description>Who would ever have thought that NI would hold an event such as this. Hundreds of Police walking around Belfast with tee shirts proclaiming their roles as police officers from all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirkistown R4</title>
      <link>/2013-07-24-kirkistown-r4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-07-24-kirkistown-r4/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}
Another windy night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirkistown R3</title>
      <link>/2013-06-26-kirkistown-r3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-06-26-kirkistown-r3/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ards Crit</title>
      <link>/2013-06-19-ards-crit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-06-19-ards-crit/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coastal Challenge</title>
      <link>/2013-06-16-coastal-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-06-16-coastal-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Once again the club ran the Coast Challenge which saw 950+ cyclists take to the roads around the peninsula.
{{ more }} The atmosphere at this years event was on of the best yet due in no part to the mild dry day and the new sign on area, which seemed to allow people to mingle better. Once again Flo and her sign on team did a great job and everything went very smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Kirkistown R2</title>
      <link>/2013-05-29-kirkistown-r2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-05-29-kirkistown-r2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2013/2013-05-29-kirkistown-r2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Another Lovely Saturday</title>
      <link>/2013-05-18-another-lovely-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-05-18-another-lovely-saturday/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The race organisers have given in to the inevitable and the North West 200 road races have been abandoned.&amp;rdquo;
Most of the spectators had already given up and left their positions on the circuit.
The grandstand at the start/finish line is empty and there is a great sense of frustration here as we have managed just a couple of laps of action.
Five races were scheduled for today but only two circuits of the Supersport class were completed before that race was red flagged when a rider came off his bike at Church Corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Kirkistown R1</title>
      <link>/2013-05-01-kirkistown-r1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-05-01-kirkistown-r1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2013/2013-05-01-kirkistown-r1-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Cannondale Complete</title>
      <link>/2013-05-01-project-cannondale-complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-05-01-project-cannondale-complete/</guid>
      <description>The Wheels arrived this morning, fitted some tyres just needs a test spin.
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Cannondale Nears Completion</title>
      <link>/2013-04-23-project-cannondale-nears-completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-04-23-project-cannondale-nears-completion/</guid>
      <description>{{ more }}
Just the bar tape to fit. Waiting for the wheels! I had my first ride this morning and all was ok don&amp;rsquo;t think I will have too many adjustment to make.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Cannondale</title>
      <link>/2013-04-13-project-cannondale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-04-13-project-cannondale/</guid>
      <description>Got of to a slow start as I ordered the wrong type of chainset.
{{ more }}
Frame £549.00 FSA Chainset £99.00 SLR Saddle £30 Front Mech Rear Mech </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collarbone on the Mend</title>
      <link>/2013-04-10-collarbone-on-the-mend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-04-10-collarbone-on-the-mend/</guid>
      <description>Visited the Ulster today for an update on my broken Clavicle, managed to get an early appointment (09:15) hoping that we would beat the cues.
{{ more }} I was called quite quickly and as expected sent to the x-ray department for a current x-ray. Back to the fracture clinic and I was seen by the Dr I was first seen by a few days after my accident and he was please with my progress, and in fact discharged me there and then, but not before I saw a Physo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cycling Once Again and CP out of Action</title>
      <link>/2013-04-07-cycling-once-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-04-07-cycling-once-again/</guid>
      <description>Lovely weather on Sat and I was stuck inside on the turbo not too happy so I decided if Sunday was a nice day I would brave the road on Flo&amp;rsquo;s Mountain Bike.
{{ more }} Sunday arrived and looked promising, so taking the bull by the horns off we set to join the Haw Rd run. All went well no pain etc except for one scare when someone fell off in front of me at a junction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spires GP or Crash Fest</title>
      <link>/2013-03-02-spires-gp-or-crash-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-03-02-spires-gp-or-crash-fest/</guid>
      <description>And it Begins 1 hour in casualty to confirm broken collar bone.
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye January Hello Cork</title>
      <link>/2013-02-04-goodbye-january-hello-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-02-04-goodbye-january-hello-cork/</guid>
      <description>Finally January has given way to February and not soon enough as far as I am concerned, the weather has been appalling wet dull and cold and that was a good day, in fact it was the dullest Jan for 50yrs in some parts of the country.
{{ more }}
The drive down was not great due to heavy traffic, and a couple of accidents so it was 21:00 when we arrived starving but more of that later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saturday&#39;s Club Run and Jekyll Blog</title>
      <link>/2013-01-13-saturdays-club-run-and-jekyll-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-01-13-saturdays-club-run-and-jekyll-blog/</guid>
      <description>A dark damp morning once again, must get lights for tomorrow. Got over to Bangor for my first Peninsula ride with the club this Year and for quite sometime.
{{ more }}
Managed to get around the Peninsula ok felt a bit tired on some of the drags on the way home, to be expected I suppose considering the head wind we hand on the way down. Once again the riding in the group left a lot to be desired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Years Day</title>
      <link>/2013-01-01-new-years-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-01-01-new-years-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Garth and Helena went back home on Saturday morning, after the normal dire service we have come to expect in our airports. So Flo and I went back to bed, well Flo did I did some things on the computer related to this blog, oh yes just rembered I changed the YAML front matter to suit the Jekyll blog software that I intend to use. Then we dandered down the town and had coffee. The rest of the day I think we lazed around and watched TV.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquablue New Club</title>
      <link>/2012-12-08-aquablue-new-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-12-08-aquablue-new-club/</guid>
      <description>A pre Christmas trip to Cork was the order of the day, arriving late afternoon we quickly got settled and then went to the Silver Key for a meal with Flo&amp;rsquo;s Mother.
{{ more }}
Sunday morning and I had planned a ride out with John. As is the norm with John all is not what it seem and he has a test the next day, and only wanted a short easy ride, but he had made arrangements for me to go with his new club Aqua Blue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chain Reaction Cycles Tour</title>
      <link>/2012-10-01-chain-reaction-cycles-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-10-01-chain-reaction-cycles-tour/</guid>
      <description>The Club organised an interesting tour of CRC tonight, some mind blowing facts turnover 160 million, 97000 products, 3 distribution company s 4 warehouses and 100 employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cork</title>
      <link>/2012-09-27-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-09-27-cork/</guid>
      <description>Brendan Kirk rang last night to see if I would go for a cycle today so we arranged to go out at 08:00 which suites me as we where going to Cork this afternoon, got back about 11:30 and after a quick shower off we went. On The way we callen in to the Java Republic shop and narurally had a coffe and bought some to bring home.
Friday Afternoon we went in to Cork City and Flo enquired about upgrading her camera to a 7D but later advice reccommened a D60 so we will have to see, I bought a new diary for next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out on the Bike Again</title>
      <link>/2012-09-17-out-on-the-bike-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-09-17-out-on-the-bike-again/</guid>
      <description>First run on the bike after 10 day off took it easy so leg not too bad.
Flo off work for two week with her back this weeks holiday cancelled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirkistown R5</title>
      <link>/2012-08-22-kirkistown-r5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-08-22-kirkistown-r5/</guid>
      <description>Another Windy night but once again we got the best of the weather. I was able to stay in the group with a fair amount of ease, didn&amp;rsquo;t contest the sprint as it was a bit manic as usual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ardill-Patterson Trophy RR</title>
      <link>/2012-08-08-ardill-patterson-trophy-rr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-08-08-ardill-patterson-trophy-rr/</guid>
      <description>Great race finished quite well, fast hard course. Another superb evenings weather</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dromara Hilly 125</title>
      <link>/2012-08-05-dromara-hilly-125/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-08-05-dromara-hilly-125/</guid>
      <description>John and Mairead came up from Cork to ride the hilly 125, the weather on the day was shite with heavy rain for the first hour and a half. No way would I have started if they hadn&amp;rsquo;t come up. It was warm which was about the best you could say, anyway I quite enjoyed the day.
After showers etc. we went to the Parlour at the Old Cross for tea, first time here and it was grand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madigan GP</title>
      <link>/2012-08-04-madigan-gp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-08-04-madigan-gp/</guid>
      <description>Great day out first over 50s race and second place, even the weather was on my side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirkistown R4</title>
      <link>/2012-07-25-kirkistown-r4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-07-25-kirkistown-r4/</guid>
      <description>Lovely evening another hard night fastest yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus first ride</title>
      <link>/2012-07-10-focus-first-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-07-10-focus-first-ride/</guid>
      <description>A dry morning at last took the new bike round the Peninsula this morning, it rode well but after talking to Garth I think I will change the bars to the same as my other bikes, the drops are just much nicer. The gears are much crisper when changing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big 50</title>
      <link>/2012-07-06-the-big-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-07-06-the-big-50/</guid>
      <description>Well to day finally came, never really thought it would. Woke up an Flo had lots of cards and presents for me to open, but the special one was my new Focus Cayo fortunately it was too wet to go out on it.
Using the old reliable Cannondale I went for coffee in Bowbells and got soaked on the way there. Friday evening We meet up with the Perrys and McCoshes in Daft Eddys for a meal and some crac, we had a great night and the children where very well behaved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirkistown R3</title>
      <link>/2012-06-27-kirkistown-r3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-06-27-kirkistown-r3/</guid>
      <description>Very hard night strong wind DNF Body&amp;rsquo;s everywhere</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coastal Challenge</title>
      <link>/2012-06-17-coastal-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-06-17-coastal-challenge/</guid>
      <description>That time again, what can I say thankfully it’s done for another year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirkistown R2</title>
      <link>/2012-05-30-kirkistown-r2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-05-30-kirkistown-r2/</guid>
      <description>A very hard night managed to hang on for 8 place</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Down GP and Daft Eddys</title>
      <link>/2012-05-26-west-down-gp-and-daft-eddys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-05-26-west-down-gp-and-daft-eddys/</guid>
      <description>West Down GP was run off on a lovely sunny day with a brutal wind which once again put a damper on the racing. A bunch speint it was with a down hill and tail wind assisted finish at over 40 mph I decided to let this one pass
On Sunday Flo and I went out for a spin to Daft Eddys, it was a lovely day but Flo was a bit sick so we had to cut the run short.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Down GP</title>
      <link>/2012-05-20-north-down-gp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-05-20-north-down-gp/</guid>
      <description>Time for the North Down GP, where do I start. Lots of talk in the days before the race, needless to say all a lot of hot air. Once again NDCC riders chasing each other down and even trying to knock each other off during the KOH Prem The head wind to D’dee helped keep a lid on the race as no one would ride in the wind, but tha tail wind on the Warren Rd made for a very fast run over Orlock , I Suppose the Finish line crash was more or less inevitable with riders dying and switching all over the place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celtic Chrono</title>
      <link>/2012-05-13-celtic-chrono/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-05-13-celtic-chrono/</guid>
      <description>After months of preparation, 34 of the world’s elite women time trial cyclists from 12 countries took part in the Celtic Chrono at Stormont Estate with local Olympian, Wendy Houvenaghel triumphant.
The elite women cyclists rode the 22 mile track with Wendy Houvenaghel, riding for Team GB in the Olympics in London, recording the fastest time on the trial of 48mins 35.09 seconds.
Wendy triumphed ahead of Olga Zabelinskaya from Russia on a time of 48 mins 57.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rás Loughguile</title>
      <link>/2012-05-06-ras-loughguile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-05-06-ras-loughguile/</guid>
      <description>I rode the Rás Loughguile today, the race started in lovely sunshine but we where soon meet with driving hail and when we went over Ora it snowed.I got away on the second lap when the first of the hail started and managed to stay away for a whole lap, I was nearly caught but the hail returned and the bunch eased off. On the Climb of Ora a smal group got away and because of the filthy conditions they managed to stay away to the finish, several crashes on the descent saw some riders face down in the bog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuji Upgrade</title>
      <link>/2012-04-20-fuji-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-04-20-fuji-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Fitted new forks, brakes &amp;amp; cables and a front mech to the Fuji. I also put new FSA compact bars on the Red Cannondale and my Felt, I have not been able to try the Felt yet but the Cannondale is fantastic, I can ride on the drops for long periods with out any problems, so I have ordered a set for the Fuji.
I had just finished all this when Flo complained about a clicking noise coming from the rear of Coppi, Further examination showed the rear wheel was nackered, hub and drive side cones gone, so I ordered a wheel from Chain Reaction, my next job when we get back from Cork on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter Weekend</title>
      <link>/2012-04-10-easter-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-04-10-easter-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Easter Saturday was a lovely day and I enjoyed the club run to Portaferry, nice and fast on the way down helped by the brisk tail wind. On the way back everyone was quite relaxed with few changes if any, my legs where still stiff from Thursday so I opted not to go over the Brae.
Sunday and Monday where very unproductive with Paris Roubaix and then MotoGP both of which where compelling viewing, Boonen&amp;rsquo;s win in Roubaix was fantastic as was lorenzo&amp;rsquo;s in Qatar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knockagh at Last </title>
      <link>/2012-03-27-knockagh-at-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-03-27-knockagh-at-last/</guid>
      <description>Finally Marty and I got to Knockagh Monument today, 1 year and three attempts later. We couldn&amp;rsquo;t have picked a better day, sunny and warm 20c light winds what more could you ask for. 75 miles in total quite tired tonight, still well worth it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carn Wheelers Classic </title>
      <link>/2012-03-25-carn-wheelers-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-03-25-carn-wheelers-classic/</guid>
      <description>Fantastic day today 22c in March, raced in shorts and bare arms. Good course and a well run race. Clifford Blayney won the A4 race and I finished 7th very happy. Huge field 80 riders and the usual morons who can&amp;rsquo;t ride there bikes. Ended in a bunch sprint pushing and shoving all over the place. Flo and Lotti where my support team and Flo got some great Photos and even managed to feed me</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John and Mairead Visit</title>
      <link>/2012-03-19-john-and-mairead-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-03-19-john-and-mairead-visit/</guid>
      <description>St Patricks was on Sat so as it is a holiday down south John and Mairea where able to come up for the weekend. John and I managed to get out on our bikes every day as the weather was unseasonably good mild and dry.
On sat we rode the club run to Portaferry, I was caught short and stopped but I was unable to catch the group, luckily they stopped for coffee and I was able to join them for the rest of the ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix GP Wedding Anniversary</title>
      <link>/2012-02-27-phoenix-gp-wedding-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-02-27-phoenix-gp-wedding-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>First race of the year, Phoenix GP At Nutts Corner all went very well felt good and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t tested at all until the end tuff drag up to the finish managed to hang on for 8th place. Not a hard course just hope I can continue in the same vain in the coming races. Great day for the club as the two Noels took first and second in the over 50&amp;rsquo;s race while Matty won the A3 race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bokhara</title>
      <link>/2012-02-20-bokhara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-02-20-bokhara/</guid>
      <description>Had a lovely Meal in the Bokhara with Flo the went to the club rooms and collected my 2012 Licence. Next Tim&amp;rsquo;s place for a Coastal Challenge meeting, good meeting lots talked about and some good ideas about this years event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garth Traveling Tomorrow</title>
      <link>/2012-01-25-garth-traveling-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-01-25-garth-traveling-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Spoke to Garth this after noon and he has book a Flight on Thursday to Heathrow arriving at 20:30 he will be staying in the Nova hotel and driving to Birmingham on Friday morning. Must ring him on Sat unless he get me first.
Did my Bowbell route this morning very windy once again but it turned out not as nasty as it could have been. Talked to Noel about the Rider Support Program and he was of the same opinion as myself, in that it was a bit elitist, and most of the club would not benefit from the program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dree Hill &amp; Roma&#39;s</title>
      <link>/2012-01-23-dree-hill-and-romas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-01-23-dree-hill-and-romas/</guid>
      <description>Headed over to Dromara and on over Dree Hill today, not sure it was one of my better ideas. Dree Hill was as hard as usual I was even chased up by a hedge cutter, but we got there in the end, alough I don&amp;rsquo;t think I had enough to eat and I ran out of energy on the way home, a hard day as it was a head wind out and quite cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calmer To Day</title>
      <link>/2012-01-17-calmer-to-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-01-17-calmer-to-day/</guid>
      <description>Good ride with Marty today a few hills over Drumbo direction, then Daft Eddies for coffee and scones.
Helped Garth download Travel Councilers emails to his account. looks like they are going to change companys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Sunday</title>
      <link>/2012-01-15-easy-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-01-15-easy-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Started today off with a nice cycle and of course Coffee in Mountstewart, weather for once was quite nice but cold, dry roads for the first time in what seems like weeks.
This afternoon I decided to try and install Pie Crust a web site generator,I think I have it working just need to discover how to create content. Of course before I could install Pie Crust I had to tidy up my test web sites so some where deleted, and I move Pie Crust &amp;amp; Chronicle to the virtual host directory on kzone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felt Cracked Frame</title>
      <link>/2011-08-30-felt-cracked-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 14:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-08-30-felt-cracked-frame/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mountstewart</title>
      <link>/2011-08-14-mountstewart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 15:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-08-14-mountstewart/</guid>
      <description>Mountstewart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Route</title>
      <link>/2011-06-08-route/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-08-route/</guid>
      <description>Itinerary
Click on the Route taken Links to show that days route and details
Day 1
Sat 28 May Newtownards – Wicklow 145 miles
Route taken
Day 2
Sun 29 May Wicklow – Dungarvan 120 miles
Route taken
Day 3
Mon 30 May Dungarvan – Skibbereen 106 miles
Route taken
Day 4
Tues 31 May Skibbereen – Killarney 107 miles
Route taken
Day 5
Wed 1 June Rest Day Killarney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Round Ireland Trip Finished</title>
      <link>/2011-06-07-round-ireland-trip-finished/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-07-round-ireland-trip-finished/</guid>
      <description>Rest day over and the legs felt slightly better, today is a long ride to Galway and the weather is damp to start with. Today turned out to be one of the best days riding yet, a nice cross tail wind warm and sunny. Once again the pace was fast for such a long day 138 miles.
Galway to Donegal Town via Sligo, where I finally lost patents with Noel who was continual going faster in heavy traffic, just too dangerous trying to keep up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrived - safe &#43; sound</title>
      <link>/2011-06-05-arrived-safe-sound/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-05-arrived-safe-sound/</guid>
      <description>All in &amp;hellip; in more ways than one!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballycastle</title>
      <link>/2011-06-05-ballycastle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-05-ballycastle/</guid>
      <description>Just waiting for lads to arrive when who stopped say hello cos he saw the club van (Joe Barr, no less) doing a reckie for an &amp;ldquo;end to end&amp;rdquo; later in the year. Rain really starting to come down now&amp;hellip;yeuch!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold and wet!</title>
      <link>/2011-06-05-cold-and-wet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-05-cold-and-wet/</guid>
      <description>Clothes changed and sandwiches scoffed and a hot drink and away in half an hour!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 9 - the final leg ...</title>
      <link>/2011-06-05-day-9-the-final-leg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-05-day-9-the-final-leg/</guid>
      <description>Just one tea stop this morning and then on to the Londonderry Arms in Carnlough for lunch. They are now checking the map to see if any flatter route is available but Martyn keeps mentioning Tor Head&amp;hellip;time will tell!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kilroot</title>
      <link>/2011-06-05-kilroot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-05-kilroot/</guid>
      <description>Martyn decided to ride on from Carnlough due to weather and wanted to go his own pace&amp;hellip; After yet another puncture, this time though it was Keith and not Peter, others arrived for final tea stop. Will meet up in the square for final photo shoot!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter and his punctures!</title>
      <link>/2011-06-05-peter-and-his-punctures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-05-peter-and-his-punctures/</guid>
      <description>Peter has had the worst luck with tyres and tubes&amp;hellip;took one of the spare wheels so hopefully will get no more today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The advance party!</title>
      <link>/2011-06-05-the-advance-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-05-the-advance-party/</guid>
      <description>Enjoying a quick beverage at the open house in Ards with Marty waiting for the others to arrive!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Londonderry Arms</title>
      <link>/2011-06-05-the-londonderry-arms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-05-the-londonderry-arms/</guid>
      <description>Got my coffee and have picked up an American back-packer, Bill, trying to get to Larne on a day when there are no buses from Portrush to Larne&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Stack Centre</title>
      <link>/2011-06-04-blue-stack-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-04-blue-stack-centre/</guid>
      <description>Up bright &amp;amp; breezy this morning to the sound of a cuckoo outside &amp;hellip; lovely &amp;amp; quiet up here so it made the snoring sound almost calming.
Currently awaiting the arrival of Philip Downie &amp;amp; Matthew McGinley at around 8am for the trip up the Inishowen Peninsula via Letterkenny and until the ferry at Greencastle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foyle Ferry - another one missed !!!</title>
      <link>/2011-06-04-foyle-ferry-another-one-missed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-04-foyle-ferry-another-one-missed/</guid>
      <description>What with all the photos at Malin Head it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like they will make the 5pm ferry. Will just have to have some tea (for a change!) and wait for the 6 o&amp;rsquo;clock one&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head wind and punctures!</title>
      <link>/2011-06-04-head-wind-and-punctures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-04-head-wind-and-punctures/</guid>
      <description>MA head wind the whole way to Malin Head but a tail wind back to the ferry at Greencastle. Ran out of hot water but once again Irish hospitality wins out when a local cafe, between Malin town and Malin Head filled the flask for me&amp;hellip;
Lots of photo opportunities at the most northerly point of Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letterkenny</title>
      <link>/2011-06-04-letterkenny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-04-letterkenny/</guid>
      <description>Looking out over Lough Swilly for tea this morning. Trying to figure out the route to Malin Head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malin for lunch</title>
      <link>/2011-06-04-malin-for-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-04-malin-for-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Before heading out to the Head. Then on around to Greencastle to get the ferry to Magilligan and back to Norn Iron&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portrush</title>
      <link>/2011-06-04-portrush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-04-portrush/</guid>
      <description>Just fed and watered. Off to bed now! Some very tired bodies &amp;hellip;
another lovely hostel. Once I get home with some more time I&amp;rsquo;ll add a list of the hostels where we stayed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top of the country</title>
      <link>/2011-06-04-top-of-the-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-04-top-of-the-country/</guid>
      <description>Joined by Philip and Matthew the lads headed off to Matthews home town of Letterkenny. Cooler and breezier today. Sorry John but the camera didn&amp;rsquo;t capture you this morning!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballyhaunis</title>
      <link>/2011-06-03-ballyhaunis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-03-ballyhaunis/</guid>
      <description>Sun cream being liberally applied after tea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dinner in Donegal</title>
      <link>/2011-06-03-dinner-in-donegal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-03-dinner-in-donegal/</guid>
      <description>Had a nice bar meal in the Abbey Hotel on the diamond in Donegal. Left Noel and John off at the pub in Letterbarra&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donegal</title>
      <link>/2011-06-03-donegal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-03-donegal/</guid>
      <description>Made it with no afternoon tea stop as I came on ahead to have a quick cycle myself. Found the lads in the bar!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galway</title>
      <link>/2011-06-03-galway/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-03-galway/</guid>
      <description>John &amp;ldquo;boomerang&amp;rdquo; Brown returned yesterday and lead the willing astray last night in the city&amp;hellip; In bed very late / early depending on your viewpoint****! So Noel asked for an early teastop this morning&amp;hellip;
Meeting up in Ballyhaunis (starting point for the Tour of Mayo).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burren</title>
      <link>/2011-06-02-burren/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-02-burren/</guid>
      <description>Was tasked to take photos of the famous limestone landscape in this part of the world - just lovely and the warm sun makes everything easier. Martyn&amp;rsquo;s superglued tyre eventually gave way in the heat and he had to change wheels before leaving teastop. Keith changed lenses to sunnies ! Yahoo !!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movin&#39; Out</title>
      <link>/2011-06-02-movin-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-02-movin-out/</guid>
      <description>Farewell to Killarney and off towards Galway - another long day, still aiming to be at overnight stop in Galway for 6pm. Heatwave due but has not yet materialised in Kerry so headed off in mizzle - or as they say down here &amp;ldquo;its a grand soft day&amp;rdquo; !
Martyn got taped evidence of snoring in the dorm last night and will play it for anyone who will listen !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrambled Eggs</title>
      <link>/2011-06-02-scrambled-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-02-scrambled-eggs/</guid>
      <description>They reckoned protein was needed this morning so scrambled eggs on toast it was. Peter got a lesson in microwave use&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shannon Ferry</title>
      <link>/2011-06-02-shannon-ferry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-02-shannon-ferry/</guid>
      <description>Kept on going in Listowel in an attempt to catch the 10:30 ferry to Killimer but without success, just arrived as it pulled away from the quay ! The summer ferry i e every half hour doesn&amp;rsquo;t start until tomorrow&amp;hellip; so tea, coffee and fig rolls all round.
No so much wind today and warming up well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snoozles Hostel</title>
      <link>/2011-06-02-snoozles-hostel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-02-snoozles-hostel/</guid>
      <description>Reconnecting with their mid-spent youth (while waiting for Martyn, there&amp;rsquo;s a surprise!)&amp;hellip; Off to Bar 8 for some grub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanish Point</title>
      <link>/2011-06-02-spanish-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-02-spanish-point/</guid>
      <description>Got here and realised that not only are we not going through Limerick we are not even going through the county! But in any case another limerick was composed&amp;hellip;
There once was a rider called Pete, who was fond of the occasional tweet, he rode so well after taking a gel, now he&amp;rsquo;s the man to beat !!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ungerts Bakery - Ennistymon</title>
      <link>/2011-06-02-ungerts-bakery-ennistymon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-02-ungerts-bakery-ennistymon/</guid>
      <description>Couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist stopping at this brightly coloured bakery for some cakes for afternoon tea - and the pastrys were good too !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Round Ireland Trip</title>
      <link>/2011-06-01-round-ireland-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 14:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-01-round-ireland-trip/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we reached the half way point of our trip, and a hard old slogg it&amp;rsquo;s been. Saturday was the longest day with busy roads and some showers early on, I could have easily stopped there and then it was just a horrible day, But we Finely reached Wicklow.
Sunday started with heavy rain and strong cross winds, which soon turned into a strong head wind which was to be with us untill we reached Mizzen on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Shop at Muckross House</title>
      <link>/2011-06-01-coffee-shop-at-muckross-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-01-coffee-shop-at-muckross-house/</guid>
      <description>Coffee indoors today and a quick walk / cycle around the lake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noel&#39;s Half-Term Report</title>
      <link>/2011-06-01-noels-half-term-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-01-noels-half-term-report/</guid>
      <description>Well, its the halfway point in the trip and time to reflect on the journey so far. When planning this trip my main concern was not the huge daily mileage but the weather and in particular the wind. My concern was justified as the strong winds played a role in our progress and morale&amp;hellip;.
An early start saw 5 riders leave from Ards Town Hall, battling south westerly winds, but by the end of the day, in Wicklow, we had lost 1 rider who returned the following morning by train.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rest Day !?!</title>
      <link>/2011-06-01-rest-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-06-01-rest-day/</guid>
      <description>Only Keith and myself taking this seriously - the others are just doing &amp;ldquo;few&amp;rdquo; miles to spin their legs out &amp;hellip; or that&amp;rsquo;s what Noel said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring of Fire !</title>
      <link>/2011-05-31-ring-of-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 22:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-31-ring-of-fire/</guid>
      <description>Marty has proposed that Johnny Cash&amp;rsquo;s song as the theme for the week - don&amp;rsquo;t ask me ask him !!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bantry</title>
      <link>/2011-05-31-bantry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-31-bantry/</guid>
      <description>A bit of a tail wind, at last ! Stopped for lunch before hitting the Caha Pass and Molls Gap. Sun still shining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>/2011-05-31-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-31-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Heading for Mizen Head and then on to Killarney. Joined by John Preston from Cork on his day off from Douglas Cycles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenmare for pm tea</title>
      <link>/2011-05-31-kenmare-for-pm-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-31-kenmare-for-pm-tea/</guid>
      <description>A hard climb over Caha but all down for tea within a few minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killarney - Martyn on his back !</title>
      <link>/2011-05-31-killarney-martyn-on-his-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-31-killarney-martyn-on-his-back/</guid>
      <description>Fell on our feet at the hostel - mixed dorm and met a sports masseuse ! Harry - her hands are softer than yours !!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mizen Head</title>
      <link>/2011-05-31-mizen-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-31-mizen-head/</guid>
      <description>Got to the most south westerly point in Ireland for coffee. Beautiful sunshine - did I really say that !!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toormore</title>
      <link>/2011-05-31-toormore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-31-toormore/</guid>
      <description>On the way out to Mizen Head managed to get one shot of them on their bikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clonakilty for tea</title>
      <link>/2011-05-30-clonakilty-for-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-30-clonakilty-for-tea/</guid>
      <description>I met up with an old pal in Clon. and had a coffee when the boys rolled in. Wind in the face taking it out of them - relentless was the term bandied about &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 3 - Dungarvan to Skibbereen</title>
      <link>/2011-05-30-day-3-dungarvan-to-skibbereen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-30-day-3-dungarvan-to-skibbereen/</guid>
      <description>Set off in sunny (but breezy) conditions - better than the weather forecast last night ! Better sleep had by all, in fact, Keith &amp;amp; I slept out as Keith&amp;rsquo;s alarm did not go off&amp;hellip; Will meet them on their arrival in Passage West off the ferry and then to John &amp;amp; Mairead&amp;rsquo;s for lunch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunch</title>
      <link>/2011-05-30-day-3-dungarvan-to-skibbereen-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-30-day-3-dungarvan-to-skibbereen-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Met the lads off the ferry at Passage West this morning and on to John and Mairead&amp;rsquo;s for lunch. A really bad shower between the ferry and the house but dry enough to continue &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovery !</title>
      <link>/2011-05-30-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-30-recovery/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s all about the recovery - the word according to Martyn &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talking Cork !!!</title>
      <link>/2011-05-30-talking-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-30-talking-cork/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m getting some slagging over my accent and how much I have speeded up when conversing with the locals ! I thought I was doing ok with the interpretations &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thursday is Limerick day...</title>
      <link>/2011-05-30-thursday-is-limerick-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-30-thursday-is-limerick-day/</guid>
      <description>In more ways than one ! We will be passing through and we want to know if you can top this &amp;ldquo;Four guys from the club did go, on a road trip round Ireland with Flo, they battled the weather drank Guinness together, and now their average is low&amp;rdquo; !!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>/2011-05-29-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-29-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately lost John Brown this morning as his ear driving him nuts ! Left him off at the train station in Wicklow - he&amp;rsquo;s off by train to Belfast and his bike is being kept for parts &amp;hellip;
Just heard coffee [and carrot cake ] being had in Gorey en route to meet up with me in Wexford.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungarvan</title>
      <link>/2011-05-29-dungarvan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-29-dungarvan/</guid>
      <description>A lovely spin from Tramore along the &amp;ldquo;Copper Coast&amp;rdquo; to Dungarvan - great views&amp;hellip; All quite tired now, just had a quick walk and off to bed. Will upload some more photos when I get some time tomorrow - only 106 miles !!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunch, Wexford</title>
      <link>/2011-05-29-lunch-wexford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-29-lunch-wexford/</guid>
      <description>Just set up lunch on the Duncannon road outside Wexford. Overlooking windfarm and Saltee Islands off the coast. Lunch is courtesy of the Keanes, special thanks to Louise for the rocky roads !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandwiches</title>
      <link>/2011-05-29-sandwiches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-29-sandwiches/</guid>
      <description>When they saw the tray of sandwiches they thought they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t do them justice but they managed !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Stop</title>
      <link>/2011-05-29-tea-stop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-29-tea-stop/</guid>
      <description>First ferry journey today from Ballyhack to Passage East then to Tramore for a final cuppa before last leg to Dungarvan. Just heard David McCann won the final stage of the Tad and with Martin Irvine winning yesterday&amp;rsquo;s stage that&amp;rsquo;s been a great week for super masseur Harry Adams - well done !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balbriggan</title>
      <link>/2011-05-28-balbriggan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-28-balbriggan/</guid>
      <description>Arrived at stop with a newcomer! So 6 for a few miles&amp;hellip;. John is threatening to get in the van in Blackrock! Faces a little tired looking now - head wind taking its toll. Guy came up to us in the car park as he had done the Coastal Challenge in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackrock - Dublin</title>
      <link>/2011-05-28-blackrock-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-28-blackrock-dublin/</guid>
      <description>Still windy but has warmed up a lot - up to about 22c. Stopped in Blackrock Park, nice view over Dublin Bay. Last leg today so I&amp;rsquo;m off to Wicklow town to find the hostel and get checked in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First stop - Newry</title>
      <link>/2011-05-28-first-stop-newry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-28-first-stop-newry/</guid>
      <description>Got to the correct spot just outside Newry and the lads rolled up about 30 minutes later. Strong headwind but they had stayed fairly dry. Quick scone and coffee - what else would you expect on a Saturday morning ! Headed off towards Dublin. Next stop Balbriggan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They&#39;re Off !</title>
      <link>/2011-05-28-theyre-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-28-theyre-off/</guid>
      <description>Bright and early this morning five cyclists left from Newtownards Town Hall on a trip around Ireland, overcast &amp;amp; windy (no change there then !). All well on time, except Martyn, who insisted it was all due to the security alerts in Belfast last night&amp;hellip;. yeh yeh Set off towards Comber and as soon as they had left the square it began to spit with rain - but it did not appear to come to much, unless it is following them&amp;hellip; Will try to keep you updated when I get a wi-fi signal &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wicklow - Captain Halpin&#39;s Bunkhouse</title>
      <link>/2011-05-28-wicklow-captain-halpins-bunkhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-28-wicklow-captain-halpins-bunkhouse/</guid>
      <description>Arrived in WIcklow at about 5pm and the lads advised just after 6pm - good time for 145 miles! Some incidents to report &amp;hellip; 1stly Peter had a run in with a small dog but not noticed until too late, skilfully avoided. John did complete the entire day, was feeing better by the time he got to Blackrock - I think the heat assisted. From Blackrock to Wicklow Noel just took one wrong road and they ended up in Greystones - they tell me its a lovely town and was well worth the visit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preparations</title>
      <link>/2011-05-19-preparations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-19-preparations/</guid>
      <description>Well underway - final number of riders still to be confirmed 4 or 5, will just have to wait until 7:30am on Saturday 28th !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shity Day</title>
      <link>/2011-05-18-shity-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-18-shity-day/</guid>
      <description>The day started badly when updating kzone from my phone while still in bed, the job failed for no reason. After breakfast and much googling and one false start, I discovered that a backup job which ran during the night had copied files locally and filled the drive, after deleting them, all was back to normal. Getting sidetracked I was looking on the web when the monitor went dark. Out came the laptop and PC World had them in stock reserved one to collect and off we went to collect it, guess what, correct none in stock except display models, wasted journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour Of the Glens</title>
      <link>/2011-05-01-tour-of-the-glens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 17:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-05-01-tour-of-the-glens/</guid>
      <description>Road the Tour of the Glens today for the first time in about eight years. We had the best weather for many a year, except for the brutal 60 mile cross head wind all the way home. The wind was so strong that in places I could not take my hand off the bars to drink, and I was nearly blown off on the battery. Apart for the wind the ride was great with the hills not seeming as hard as I remembered, perhaps it was the blue sky and warm sunshine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter</title>
      <link>/2011-04-29-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 08:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-04-29-easter/</guid>
      <description>With the weather remaining excellent for this time of year, we have got lots of things done. Thanks to Tim who supplied some manure , we where able to plant our Veg garden Broccoli, Carrots, Sweet Pea, Strawberries and Corvettes.
Easter Tue and it was the Club Easter Ramble to Newcastle, an over cast cool windy day and busy roads, 12 of us did the ride with lunch in Mauds. This was my second 100 miler this month, I thing the fact that the club where all in Mallorca doing big miles helped with the motivation and once again April is my highest mileage month so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busier March</title>
      <link>/2011-03-31-busier-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-03-31-busier-march/</guid>
      <description>March saw a trip to Cork to visit Flo&amp;rsquo;s uncle Hugh, who had just had a pacemaker fitted. On arriving at Valentine Villas Hugh was no where to be found, after some searching we found him down at the Lough watching the world going by. He was in great form and as up to date with everything as usual .
The weather was great, cold but bright and sunny so I was able to get on the bike with John on Sunday and Tuesday , on Sunday we went with some local cyclists to Fermoy and Tuesday we went to Bandon &amp;amp; Kinsale, two good 50 plus mile runs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January Done and Dusted</title>
      <link>/2011-01-31-january-done-and-dusted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 17:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011-01-31-january-done-and-dusted/</guid>
      <description>Well this month was pretty uneventful, started to get some good miles in on the bike after a disastrous December. Dry but cold with little in the way of wind which is always good.
Noel called a meeting about the around Ireland challenge, Daren was there to offer advice on training and nutrition all things we know but choose to forget. I decided to try some long zone two rides both for endurance and weight loss, time will tell how that goes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballyhoura Mountain Bike Trails</title>
      <link>/2010-10-31-ballyhoura-mountain-bike-trails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 16:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-10-31-ballyhoura-mountain-bike-trails/</guid>
      <description>After The Cooley Challenge we had promised John that we would go to Ballyhoura, after a dismal drive down in pouring rain on friday, Saturday turned out a lovely bright sunny day. 21 miles and two and a half hours later we had compleated the white run, lots of flowing single track on well maintained paths. Probably the best day I have ever had on a Mountain bike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felt Dispatch</title>
      <link>/2010-09-19-felt-dispatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 19:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-09-19-felt-dispatch/</guid>
      <description>Felt Dispatch
Friday afternoon seen the arrival of my new bike, naturaly due to the weather I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get out on it until Sunday. Flo and I went with the D&amp;rsquo;dee coffee run to Mountstewart. First impressions of the Felt are good fit seems fine just need to try the fixed wheel option.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballaghadereen</title>
      <link>/2010-09-04-ballaghadereen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 19:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-09-04-ballaghadereen/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday 31st August we travelled to Ballaghadereen Co Roscommon and the Abbeyfield hotel for 3 nights, on the drive down the weather was fantastic, stopping for coffee in Carrick-on-Shannon, on the way in to Ballaghadereen I spotted a car parts shop which we visited the next day to get a replacement Ariel for the car. On arrival in Ballaghadereen and after checking in to the hotel we went out for a short drive to see what was available for food, but we decided to eat in the hotel bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Da Cooley Challenge</title>
      <link>/2010-08-29-da-cooley-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-08-29-da-cooley-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This year Flo rode the short course and finished 4th, not bad when you consider there was over 200 entries. John Preston came up from Cork and also rode the short course and finished 11th in his class, after his mate made him turn off this heart monitor.
I had a horrible day started off well enough riding to my heart rate on the long road section but once we went off road I started getting cramps which eventually forced me to cut the course and ride back via the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flo Racing Kirkistown R3</title>
      <link>/2010-07-22-flo-racing-kirkistown-r3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 10:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-07-22-flo-racing-kirkistown-r3/</guid>
      <description>Flo putting the competition under pressure
Flo decided to try the clubs race tonight at Kirkistown. It was another warm but windy night at the county Down circuit with 60 riders taking part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coastal Challenge</title>
      <link>/2010-06-21-coastal-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 22:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-06-21-coastal-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Many weeks hard work by lots of club members paid off as this years event was one of the best yet. Superb weather saw close to 800 riders taking part. For the first time since we started running the event I was able to take photos at will, with most people happy to pose for me. The atmosphere at Barr Hall was great with everyone taking time to have lunch in the warm sunshine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracker of a Weekend</title>
      <link>/2010-05-23-cracker-of-a-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 22:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-05-23-cracker-of-a-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Dining Outside and the temp went higher
One of the best weekends in years. Cycled Saturday with the club around the Peninsula, Sunny and warm for a change.
Sunday Flo and I did the magherascouce run with coffee in Castle Espie.
Magherascouce Run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Down GP</title>
      <link>/2010-05-17-north-down-gp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 11:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-05-17-north-down-gp/</guid>
      <description>North Down GP
My First open road race since the Ards 3 day back in July 2006. A good race on a tricky rolling circuit, 7 laps some in heavy rain. All in all a good day finishing in the main group and staying at the front for as long as I could, unfortunately I had nothing left for the gallop at the end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour de Cure</title>
      <link>/2010-05-08-tour-de-cure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 22:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-05-08-tour-de-cure/</guid>
      <description>An early start was the order of the day for the 30 minute drive from Cork to Middleton and the start of the 2nd Tour de Cure endorsed by Stephen Roche one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s greatest cyclists.
Tour de Cure
Arriving early was a god send, we parked in the railway station right next to sign on, and then where able to sign just before the masses arrived. After signing on and collecting our jerseys we headed back to the car to await the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Month for Miles</title>
      <link>/2010-04-30-big-month-for-miles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-04-30-big-month-for-miles/</guid>
      <description>April is traditionally a month of big mileage, or at least has been since our club started going to Mallorca for a weeks Cycling.
This year was no exception I managed almost 800 miles before our departure on Sat 24th, however I only managed one ride over 80 miles, the bulk being around 40 - 50 miles.
Suddenly all our training looked to have been in vain as a volcano erupted in Iceland and closed most of european air space for nearly a week, leaving many people stranded abroad and many loosing holidays completely, however our luck held and the wind changed direction blowing volcanic ash away, and so on the 24 our flight departed Belfast for Palma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cycling &amp; Walking in the Mournes</title>
      <link>/2010-03-27-cycling--walking-in-themournes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-03-27-cycling--walking-in-themournes/</guid>
      <description>Marty and myself set off from Newtownards at 7:30 and cycled to Meelmore Lodge about 40 miles , where we meet up with Flo. After a quick change of clothing it was off up the trassey track to the hare&amp;rsquo;s gap where we regrouped, and following the Brandy Pad we walked round Slieve Commedagh. Turning left we headed to the mourne wall and the valley between Donard and Commedagh. We then followed th Mourne Wall over Commedagh and Back to the Hare&amp;rsquo;s gap and finaly back to Meelmore Lodge, covering about 9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XMTB McConvey Cycles Winter League 2010 Ormeau Park Race 2</title>
      <link>/2010-03-07-xmtb-mcconvey-cycles-winter-league-2010-ormeau-park-race-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 16:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2010-03-07-xmtb-mcconvey-cycles-winter-league-2010-ormeau-park-race-2/</guid>
      <description>Having see Flo enjoying the first round the previous week I decided to have a go as well, so on of the best day so far this year we head of to Ormeau Park for the race.
The course had dried out from last week and was very rideable if somewhat technical.
XMTB McConvey Cycles
Winter League 2010 Ormeau Park
Race 2 07/03/2010
Fun 8 laps
Name Club Time
Liam McGreevy Planet X 42.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back on the Bike</title>
      <link>/2009-09-07-back-on-the-bike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2009-09-07-back-on-the-bike/</guid>
      <description>Got 36 miles in today, now knackered. Going to try running tomorrow because, guess what yes it&amp;rsquo;s going to rain all day.
Good Stage in the Vuelta today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour of Ireland (St Patricks Hill)</title>
      <link>/2009-08-23-tour-of-ireland-st-patricks-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2009-08-23-tour-of-ireland-st-patricks-hill/</guid>
      <description>Arrive early so we went for a coffee, then panicked when we look up the hill and saw that there was already loads of people on the climb. Struggled up the hill and got a really good spot on the left about three quarters of the way up.
Writting on the Road
Waited for about an hour and where enterined by the kids having a ball writing on the road, with chalk provided by the Livestrong Foundation .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dromara Hilly 125km</title>
      <link>/2009-08-09-dromara-hilly-125km/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2009-08-09-dromara-hilly-125km/</guid>
      <description>Rode the Dromara Hilly 125 today after much debate, woke to pleasant morning so I had no more excuses. Not having made any travel arrangements with the club I drove down on my own and was pleased that Eric, Ian, Trevor, Noel, Harry and the Old Pro (Brian) had also made the trip, content now that I would have some good wheels to sit on I started looking forward to the days ride.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
