<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Madrid on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/madrid/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Madrid on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:57:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/madrid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Repair</title>
      <link>/2023-01-31-repair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:57:03 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/2023-01-31-repair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During or recent trip to Madrid we passed this shop selling all types of springs, later the same day we found a shop for leather workers selling everything from hide to tiny grommets, pliers, cutters and punches the list goes on. On our last day I found an arcade with 6 to 8 clock / watch shops again selling everything from watches , batteries, faces, glass iand tools to fit glass and many thing I could not identify. Never seen the like back home, looks to me like the Spanish repair stuff. Even back in Real it&amp;rsquo;s easy to get parts for things, we could learn from this back home.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2023/2023-01-31-repair-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Spring Shop&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spring Shop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madrid</title>
      <link>/2023-01-26-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2023-01-26-madrid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2023/2023-01-26-madrid-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Flo in Madrid&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flo in Madrid&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our first trip trip to Madrid, leaving from Valencia Joaquin Sorolla station on the high speed train great way to travel clean, roomy and fast.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Getting around was super easy on the metro, and number 1 and 2 buses which are free for tourists and being a big city things tented to be spread out so the transport was needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our Ibis Hotel was quite central and beside it was a fantastic taps bar where I got a fabulous scrambled egg and morcilla dish.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
