<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>france on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/france/</link>
    <description>Recent content in france on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/france/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lembras - Chinon</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-05-17-lembras-chinon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-05-17-lembras-chinon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Woke to the sound of light rain and a cold 11c, got our stuff together and hit the road as the rain got heaver.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Sebastion - Lembras</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-05-16-san-sebastion-lembras/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-05-16-san-sebastion-lembras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Moved off around 10:00 heading for Decathlon to get a second wheel bag, that done and Lotti walked we set off proper with a quick detour on and off the payage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpe d&#39;Huez</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2018-06-08-alpe-d-huez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2018-06-08-alpe-d-huez/</guid>
      <description>Rode the mythical climb for the first time in 20yrs still hard. Discovered a great road back to Allemont fantastic views.
{{ more }}
Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez
Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez
Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez
Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2018-06-06-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2018-06-06-france/</guid>
      <description>Drove back into France today. We finally relented and used the toll roads what a difference it made much better surface no where near as tiring, but a bit hard on the pocket at €55
{{ more }}
Not long after crossing the border the rain started and the temperature dropped then to make things worse the aire we had hoped to stay at in Briançon was being used as Fairground, another 5km up the road and we found an aire in Le Villard-Late St Chaffery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France and Belgium </title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2018-03-25-france-and-belgium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2018-03-25-france-and-belgium/</guid>
      <description>Saturday and we finally arrived in Kilrane and meet Frank and Catherine for lunch in Kellys, on Sunday I managed a cycle, meeting everyone for coffee in Karoo. Then at 18:00 we boarded the boat for Cherbourg
{{ more }}
Enjoyed a lovely sunny drive to Dives-Sur-Mer, where we stopped for the night in an Aire near the town.
A Stinking wet day so after a late breakfast we drove to Bapaume and parked up in the Aire bang in the center of town, a quick visit to the tourist office and the plans are in place for tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vannes</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-09-02-vannes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-09-02-vannes/</guid>
      <description>Didn&amp;rsquo;t leave Chinon until 11:45 after the Obligatory Coffee with the Lyttles, called into the Camper Van dealer but it was closed for lunch.
{{ more }}
Stopped in McDonald&amp;rsquo;s for lunch and an emergency stop in Valet for Flo and once more at an Aire. We arrive 18:00 at the Flower Camping Le Conleau setup ate our tea walked Lotti, watched Ozark and bed.
Still raining when we got up but very light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinon</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-29-chinon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-29-chinon/</guid>
      <description>Arriving in Chinon Camping de L&amp;rsquo;ile Auger around 17:30 to a blistering hot 38c which was a surprise as I expected it to be cooler further north.
St Martins {{ more }}
Setup in a nice shaded spot, put out the tarp, had tea and then walked round the town and found a café for desert.
We slept late and after a leisurely breakfast we went for a walk around the old town.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>