<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithmillar.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bugarra</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-02-08-bugarra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-02-08-bugarra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Took Lotti to the river in Bugarra for a walk and hopefully a swim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://keithmillar.github.io/images/2019/2019-02-08-bugarra.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Contemplateing a Swim&#34; /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Contemplateing a Swim&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volta a la Comunitat Valenciana</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-02-08-volta-a-la-comunitat-valenciana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-02-08-volta-a-la-comunitat-valenciana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Up early for us and on the road for 09:00 to get to Pedralba for around 10:00 so we have time to find a good parking spot for Eddy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTT - XXIII Marcha Montroy</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-01-27-btt-xxiii-marcha-montroy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-01-27-btt-xxiii-marcha-montroy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://keithmillar.github.io/images/2019/2019-01-27-BTT-XXIII-Marcha-Montroy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;BTT - XXIII Marcha Montroy&#34; /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;BTT - XXIII Marcha Montroy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunar Eclipse Blood Moon</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-01-21-lunar-eclipse-blood-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-01-21-lunar-eclipse-blood-moon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://keithmillar.github.io/images/2019/2019-01-21-lunar-eclipse-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Blood Moon&#34; /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Blood Moon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Giant Terrago </title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-01-19-terrago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-01-19-terrago/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://keithmillar.github.io/images/2019/2019-01-19-terrago.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Terrago&#34; /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;First Brief Spin On The Terrago&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas at the Douglas&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-12-25-christmas-at-the-douglass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 22:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-12-25-christmas-at-the-douglass/</guid>
      <description>Being the coldest Winter on record in Northern Ireland, and Christmas Day tempatures of -12 it was touch and go if we would be able to get to Fiona and John&amp;rsquo;s for our Lunch. Luckly the roads where clear of snow and we arrived in god time.
Once again the whole family put on a great spread of food and drink and a great day was had by all. It was good to see Kathleen, Fiona, Mark and Lisa once again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Walk</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-12-21-snow-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 22:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-12-21-snow-walk/</guid>
      <description>With the tempature hovering around -6 we decided to go for a Moonlight walk from Ards Shopping Center to Scrabo and then around the Golf course and in Killynether then returning to the car.
Marty &amp;amp; FLo
Marty &amp;amp; Flo with Flash
Scrabo Tower
Ards by Moonlight
Mysterious Tracks in the Snow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stove Installation</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-11-22-stove-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 20:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-11-22-stove-installation/</guid>
      <description>Flo in her wisdom decided that we need a multi fuel Stove here are some pics of the aftermath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ballyhoura Mountain Bike Trails</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-10-31-ballyhoura-mountain-bike-trails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 16:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-10-31-ballyhoura-mountain-bike-trails/</guid>
      <description>After The Cooley Challenge we had promised John that we would go to Ballyhoura, after a dismal drive down in pouring rain on friday, Saturday turned out a lovely bright sunny day. 21 miles and two and a half hours later we had compleated the white run, lots of flowing single track on well maintained paths. Probably the best day I have ever had on a Mountain bike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valencia Flo&#39;s 50</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-10-10-valencia-flos-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-10-10-valencia-flos-50/</guid>
      <description>On the 5th October we flew to Alicante and collected a battered hire for the drive to Valencia, as one would expect the weather was fabulous. The drive was uneventfull and we arrived at John &amp;amp; Mairead&amp;rsquo;s house mid after noon, and it didn&amp;rsquo;t take us long to get the wine on the go.
Sunny Spain
Happy 50th Birthday Flo
With glass in hand we enjoyed the weather for the rest of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felt Dispatch</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-09-19-felt-dispatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 19:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-09-19-felt-dispatch/</guid>
      <description>Felt Dispatch
Friday afternoon seen the arrival of my new bike, naturaly due to the weather I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get out on it until Sunday. Flo and I went with the D&amp;rsquo;dee coffee run to Mountstewart. First impressions of the Felt are good fit seems fine just need to try the fixed wheel option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stroke City and Donegal</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-09-11-stroke-city-and-donegal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 20:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-09-11-stroke-city-and-donegal/</guid>
      <description>Walls Of Derry
Walls Of Derry
Week two and we found ourselves in the Everglades Hotel Londonderry, arriving quite late after a trip to Chain Reaction Cycles and a lovely lunch in the Galgorm Manor. Once we had checked in to the hotel Flo was busting a gut to explore the Walls of Derry, after finding a parking place off we set. Walking through a deserted town center past the Guild Hall we climb on to the walls, taking a anti-clockwise course we explored the walls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ballaghadereen</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-09-04-ballaghadereen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 19:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-09-04-ballaghadereen/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday 31st August we travelled to Ballaghadereen Co Roscommon and the Abbeyfield hotel for 3 nights, on the drive down the weather was fantastic, stopping for coffee in Carrick-on-Shannon, on the way in to Ballaghadereen I spotted a car parts shop which we visited the next day to get a replacement Ariel for the car. On arrival in Ballaghadereen and after checking in to the hotel we went out for a short drive to see what was available for food, but we decided to eat in the hotel bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Beans</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-08-30-french-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-08-30-french-beans/</guid>
      <description>Our first French Beans and loads more on the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Da Cooley Challenge</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-08-29-da-cooley-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-08-29-da-cooley-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This year Flo rode the short course and finished 4th, not bad when you consider there was over 200 entries. John Preston came up from Cork and also rode the short course and finished 11th in his class, after his mate made him turn off this heart monitor.
I had a horrible day started off well enough riding to my heart rate on the long road section but once we went off road I started getting cramps which eventually forced me to cut the course and ride back via the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flo Racing Kirkistown R3</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-07-22-flo-racing-kirkistown-r3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 10:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-07-22-flo-racing-kirkistown-r3/</guid>
      <description>Flo putting the competition under pressure
Flo decided to try the clubs race tonight at Kirkistown. It was another warm but windy night at the county Down circuit with 60 riders taking part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s A hard Life</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-07-21-its-a-hard-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-07-21-its-a-hard-life/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a Hard Life</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wexford</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-07-14-wexford/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-07-14-wexford/</guid>
      <description>Spent some of our 12th weekend in the now traditional Kilraine. This year Richard And Yuk were also staying with their little girl Hannah. Lotti and Hannah spent most of the time avoiding each other, except in lottis case when there was the chance of Hannah dropping food.
Train leaving Kilmeadan Station
Monday was a nice day so off we all went to the Waterford &amp;amp; Suir Valley Railway, and a 50 minute (12km) journey in the above train.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coastal Challenge</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-06-21-coastal-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 22:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-06-21-coastal-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Many weeks hard work by lots of club members paid off as this years event was one of the best yet. Superb weather saw close to 800 riders taking part. For the first time since we started running the event I was able to take photos at will, with most people happy to pose for me. The atmosphere at Barr Hall was great with everyone taking time to have lunch in the warm sunshine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cracker of a Weekend</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-05-23-cracker-of-a-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 22:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-05-23-cracker-of-a-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Dining Outside and the temp went higher
One of the best weekends in years. Cycled Saturday with the club around the Peninsula, Sunny and warm for a change.
Sunday Flo and I did the magherascouce run with coffee in Castle Espie.
Magherascouce Run</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North Down GP</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-05-17-north-down-gp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 11:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-05-17-north-down-gp/</guid>
      <description>North Down GP
My First open road race since the Ards 3 day back in July 2006. A good race on a tricky rolling circuit, 7 laps some in heavy rain. All in all a good day finishing in the main group and staying at the front for as long as I could, unfortunately I had nothing left for the gallop at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour de Cure</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-05-08-tour-de-cure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 22:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-05-08-tour-de-cure/</guid>
      <description>An early start was the order of the day for the 30 minute drive from Cork to Middleton and the start of the 2nd Tour de Cure endorsed by Stephen Roche one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s greatest cyclists.
Tour de Cure
Arriving early was a god send, we parked in the railway station right next to sign on, and then where able to sign just before the masses arrived. After signing on and collecting our jerseys we headed back to the car to await the start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Month for Miles</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-04-30-big-month-for-miles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-04-30-big-month-for-miles/</guid>
      <description>April is traditionally a month of big mileage, or at least has been since our club started going to Mallorca for a weeks Cycling.
This year was no exception I managed almost 800 miles before our departure on Sat 24th, however I only managed one ride over 80 miles, the bulk being around 40 - 50 miles.
Suddenly all our training looked to have been in vain as a volcano erupted in Iceland and closed most of european air space for nearly a week, leaving many people stranded abroad and many loosing holidays completely, however our luck held and the wind changed direction blowing volcanic ash away, and so on the 24 our flight departed Belfast for Palma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycling &amp; Walking in the Mournes</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-03-27-cycling-walking-in-themournes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-03-27-cycling-walking-in-themournes/</guid>
      <description>Marty and myself set off from Newtownards at 7:30 and cycled to Meelmore Lodge about 40 miles , where we meet up with Flo. After a quick change of clothing it was off up the trassey track to the hare&amp;rsquo;s gap where we regrouped, and following the Brandy Pad we walked round Slieve Commedagh. Turning left we headed to the mourne wall and the valley between Donard and Commedagh. We then followed th Mourne Wall over Commedagh and Back to the Hare&amp;rsquo;s gap and finaly back to Meelmore Lodge, covering about 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XMTB McConvey Cycles Winter League 2010 Ormeau Park Race 2</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-03-07-xmtb-mcconvey-cycles-winter-league-2010-ormeau-park-race-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 16:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-03-07-xmtb-mcconvey-cycles-winter-league-2010-ormeau-park-race-2/</guid>
      <description>Having see Flo enjoying the first round the previous week I decided to have a go as well, so on of the best day so far this year we head of to Ormeau Park for the race.
The course had dried out from last week and was very rideable if somewhat technical.
XMTB McConvey Cycles
Winter League 2010 Ormeau Park
Race 2 07/03/2010
Fun 8 laps
Name Club Time 1. Liam McGreevy Planet X 42.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-01-31-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2010-01-31-january/</guid>
      <description>Not much happening at this time of year, so the start of the month was fairly quite. However we had a weekend away planned for the very end of the month in Co Roscommon.
Lough Key
We drove down to Ballghadereen Co Roscommon on Friday night, the drive to Enniskillen was woeful due to road works but when we crosssed the border it turned into a lovely bright moon lite night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas &amp; New Year</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-12-31-christmas-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-12-31-christmas-new-year/</guid>
      <description>Garth arrived on 18th at 05:30 and with him came the first snow of the year and freezing temperatures. After Breakfast in the travelodge it was of to Maria&amp;rsquo;s to get the dart into Dublin.
Off the DART and a cold busy Dublin awaited us. A quick walk around the city centre with a visit to HMV and the Post Office on O&amp;rsquo;Connell Street, which was pretty much the original building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portrush Weekend</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-11-13-portrush-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-11-13-portrush-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Drove up on friday afternoon traffic was light, which gave us time to admire the sunset. Fantastic as it was it was a precursor to the wild weather forecast for late Friday night and Saturday.
Arrived at the Magherabuoy House Hotel around 16:30 and relaxed in our rooms, then went for a drink in the bar and our comp meal in the hotel restaurant. An early night ready for tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>East Antrim Cyclo Cross</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-10-10-east-antrim-cyclo-cross/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-10-10-east-antrim-cyclo-cross/</guid>
      <description>First Cross event in a couple of years, super course but much too hard for the first event of the year. The course was more suited to mountain bikes than CX bikes with quite a severe down hill section with large rocks to be avoided. All of the course was ridable , but I was a bit over geared for some of the climbs. Four 3 mile laps with 2 severe climbs made this a tough event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murlough Bay Dundrum</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-10-05-murlough-bay-dundrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-10-05-murlough-bay-dundrum/</guid>
      <description>We decided to go for a walk today, and after great debate I decided on Murlough Bay just outside Dundrum. So off we set just after 10:00 rather later than I would have like, but that&amp;rsquo;s the price of indecision. Arrived in the car park just before 11:00 and off we set.
Murloch
Well what a surprise as we set off through the sand dunes, a board walk lead us to the beach, and fantastic views of the Mourne Mountains towering over Newcastle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Da Cooley Thriller Mtb XC Marathon 2009</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-09-21-da-cooley-thriller-mtb-xc-marathon-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-09-21-da-cooley-thriller-mtb-xc-marathon-2009/</guid>
      <description>Having stumbled across this event on the web, I thought I would mention it to Marty, big mistake &amp;ldquo;always wanted to do one of those&amp;rdquo; was his immediate reaction and that was it we were now fully committed. I spent the rest of the week looking for an excuse not to go but no really good one came to mind so on Friday I found myself checking over the BeOne for the adventure to follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back on the Bike</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-09-07-back-on-the-bike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-09-07-back-on-the-bike/</guid>
      <description>Got 36 miles in today, now knackered. Going to try running tomorrow because, guess what yes it&amp;rsquo;s going to rain all day.
Good Stage in the Vuelta today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour of Ireland (St Patricks Hill)</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-08-23-tour-of-ireland-st-patricks-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-08-23-tour-of-ireland-st-patricks-hill/</guid>
      <description>Arrive early so we went for a coffee, then panicked when we look up the hill and saw that there was already loads of people on the climb. Struggled up the hill and got a really good spot on the left about three quarters of the way up.
Writting on the Road
Waited for about an hour and where enterined by the kids having a ball writing on the road, with chalk provided by the Livestrong Foundation .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dromara Hilly 125km</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-08-09-dromara-hilly-125km/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2009-08-09-dromara-hilly-125km/</guid>
      <description>Rode the Dromara Hilly 125 today after much debate, woke to pleasant morning so I had no more excuses. Not having made any travel arrangements with the club I drove down on my own and was pleased that Eric, Ian, Trevor, Noel, Harry and the Old Pro (Brian) had also made the trip, content now that I would have some good wheels to sit on I started looking forward to the days ride.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>