<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blu on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/blu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blu on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/blu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blu Shakedown Run</title>
      <link>/2016-09-18-blu-shakedown-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-09-18-blu-shakedown-run/</guid>
      <description>Took Blu down to Quinton Bay for a shake down run since we completed her internal build earlier in the week.&#xA;{{ more }} All went well gas worked so we had tea and coffee, just a matter of being organised with the necessary gear for our travels I think it will require quite a few trips to sort everything out.&#xA;Played around with the mythtv it did work, likely need a better aerial or change the tuner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Update on Blu</title>
      <link>/2016-09-08-quick-update-on-blu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-09-08-quick-update-on-blu/</guid>
      <description>Not a lot posted about Blu in recent weeks / months, due mainly to being away on holiday in Canada with Garth &amp;amp; Helana. Now that we have been back for few weeks and Flo got her act together and we ordered a kitchen from Evodesign, which took around two weeks to arrive meaning another delay.&#xA;{{ more }} The flat pack arrived last Thursday and we started to assemble it over the course of the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackbirds and Blu&#39;s Insulation</title>
      <link>/2016-06-05-blackbirds-and-blus-insulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-06-05-blackbirds-and-blus-insulation/</guid>
      <description>Finally finished the vans insulation, passenger door much easier with Flo helping, still a bit of a pig. Also fix the roof so here&amp;rsquo;s hoping. {{ more }} Having watched the Blackbird chicks quite closely for over a week now the seem to have fledged early this afternoon when I wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking.&#xA;Since it is such a nice afternoon we took a spin down to Ballywalter and sat watching the world go by, while enjoying an ice cream, as we sat the mist cleared and the wind dropped a wonderful end to the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hectic month and piss poor Weather</title>
      <link>/2015-11-30-hectic-month-and-piss-poor-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2015-11-30-hectic-month-and-piss-poor-weather/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This turned out to be a totally manic month, having committed ourselves to Spain on the 13th of December and a stressful visit to Cork on the 17th, with the van not even half finished it was all hands on deck.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lotti&#39;s New Campervan</title>
      <link>/2015-09-28-lotti-s-new-campervan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2015-09-28-lotti-s-new-campervan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2015/2015-09-28-lotti-s-new-campervan-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Lotti getting to know her new Campervan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Van</title>
      <link>/2015-09-24-new-van/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2015-09-24-new-van/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
