<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Canada on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/canada/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Canada on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/canada/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Campobello Island</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-25-campobello-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-25-campobello-island/</guid>
      <description>From Saint George to Deer Island to Campobello Island two boat crossings.
Flo&amp;rsquo;s Magic Ferry {{ more }} First we had lunch in the Fireside Resturant, then we visited Roosevelt&amp;rsquo;s Cottage in the Roosevelt Campobello International Park walked around some then Jocie&amp;rsquo;s Porch for a Quick Coffee before the return trip.
Roosevelt’s Cottage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foster Brook Trail</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-23-foster-brook-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-23-foster-brook-trail/</guid>
      <description>Helena drove us to Fundy National Park and we meet up with Darrell and his walking group and we walked the Foster Brook Trail. {{ more }} Very warm today but nice in the forest. The trail was moderate with just the one steep section in the middle, and we enjoyed lunch on the Wolf Point river bank.
After the walk we went into Alma for a coffee in the Octopus Coffee shop and drove back via Suffolk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Martins &amp; Fundy Trail Parkway</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-21-st-martins-fundy-trail-parkway/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-21-st-martins-fundy-trail-parkway/</guid>
      <description>More relaxed day today drove to St Martins and them on to Fundy Trail Parkway for a walk on the beach, and then back to St Martins for an ice cream, and home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canoeing on the Kennebecasis River</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-20-canoeing-on-the-kennebecasis-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-20-canoeing-on-the-kennebecasis-river/</guid>
      <description>Canoeing on the Kennebecasis River today. Hired a car as G&amp;amp;H have a lot going on today including a T.T tonight in Hampton so to take the pressure off us we got a car for the day at a cost of $80 and $9 fuel well worth it.
Great Fun Today
{{ more }} During the course of our trip we spotted Bald Eagles, Osprey, Red-striped Blackbirds, Musk Rats and an array of dragon flys, not to mention the blood sucking flies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministers Island</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-19-ministers-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-19-ministers-island/</guid>
      <description>After doing some quick jobs down town and grabbing a quick coffee in Second Cup G &amp;amp; H pick us up and we headed of to Ministers Island.
{{ more }} Almost perfect timing saw us having to wait for about 5 minutes for the tide to clear the causeway before we could cross to the island. Once across we parked and started the walk around the islands perimeter, 2.5 hours and 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Manan</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-18-grand-manan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-18-grand-manan/</guid>
      <description>A Foggy drive to Blacks Harbour and a longer Foggy boat ride to Grand Manan.
{{ more }} After an early start we were all gasping for coffee when the boat docked we made a bee line for the first coffee shop we could find, the aromas when we opened the door where promising but we where told that this was a Roasting House and they couldn&amp;rsquo;t sell coffee, so back on the road we went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian by Night</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-13-italian-by-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-13-italian-by-night/</guid>
      <description>Our turn to treat Garth &amp;amp; Helena
G &amp;amp; H
F &amp;amp; K</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Challenge Weekend</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-08-the-challenge-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-08-the-challenge-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Today sees the start of the final prep for the races on Sat and Sunday.
Flo&amp;rsquo;s own brand wheels
{{ more }}
Friday The challenge event is starting to feel a bit more real today as we opened registration and the vendors set up their wares. Flo and I counted the barriers at the swim and bike transition. Then when Garth was free we check out Bike course especially the turn on to and off the highway, where we will be marshalling on the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another truck for Flo</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-07-another-truck-for-flo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-07-another-truck-for-flo/</guid>
      <description>Down to St Stephen to collect another 26 foot U-Haul for Flo and the Atlantic Super store for water, the truck worked out fine but there was no water for us to collect not ordered.
{{ more }} Garth and I checked out the swim course and set up the volunteer room during a massive thunder storm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthday Treat at Algonquin Golf Club</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-06-birthday-treat-at-algonquin-golf-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-06-birthday-treat-at-algonquin-golf-club/</guid>
      <description>Garth and Helena treated Flo and me to a Birthday meal in the Algonquin Golf Club, great spot with excellent food and service.
{{ more }} Coffee in Lilly Lake and a detour to St George we finally arrived back in St Andrews.
Meet Garth and set up the laptop for him, then Flo and I walked down town for a beer in the Red Herring, and the out for my Birthday celebrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collecting our Trucks</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-05-collecting-our-trucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-05-collecting-our-trucks/</guid>
      <description>Collected our trucks this morning and drove down to St Andrews. Once again the sun was shining.
Flo with her super sized Truck
{{ more }} Our trip to Saint Andrews as been cut short as Garth&amp;rsquo;s PC failed to boot, so after we got settled in Flo and I returned to Saint John to collect Garth&amp;rsquo;s old laptop and we will head back down to St Andrews tomorrow. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First trip to St Andrews</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-03-first-trip-to-st-andrews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-03-first-trip-to-st-andrews/</guid>
      <description>Pre Challenge trip to St Andrews
{{ more }} Quick out and back spin with Garth to Cape Spencer, while Helena and Flo did the same route, another lovely morning, quite impressed with the Kona.
Then we drove down to Saint Andrews for G &amp;amp; H to have a meeting with Tressa, Flo and I wandered round the town sorting things for next week and the Challenge event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subway Canada day 10k</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-01-subway-canada-day-10k/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-07-01-subway-canada-day-10k/</guid>
      <description>Garth won the 10k road race in Grand Bay-Westfield
Darrell with Garth after the run {{ more }} We stopped of at Gina and Errols this morning and collect a nice Kona CX bike for me to ride while we are here.
Then it&amp;rsquo;s off to Grand Bay-Westfiels for the Canada Day 10 mile road race, Garth running in the 10k race which he won even though Alex Coffin messed up the finish which apparently was Garth&amp;rsquo;s fault.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Village Spin</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-06-30-french-village-spin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-06-30-french-village-spin/</guid>
      <description>Adjusted Helena&amp;rsquo;s bike and Garth and I parked in the Irving Station and we headed off on the roads around French Village.
The temperature increased up to 29c but the humidity was the real killer not very nice. At one point a guy on a motor bike complement us on our speed and cornering ability. Hard roads but a lovely place, would make a nice place to build if we decide to move here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off to Canada</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-06-28-off-to-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-06-28-off-to-canada/</guid>
      <description>We got the Bus from Cork to the Airport last night and stayed in the Premier Inn as we have an early flight in the morning.
{{ more }}
First we flew Dublin to St John&amp;rsquo;s, Newfoundland and connect to Halifax Nova Scotia the flights all went well and we where pleasantly surprised by the heat in St John&amp;rsquo;s.
Garth and Helena picked us up from Halifax and we arrived in Saint Johns NB around 19:00 the weather on the way down was lovely until we reached G&amp;amp;H and it clouded over but still very warm and humid.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>