<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>race on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/race/</link>
    <description>Recent content in race on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/race/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ronde Van Vlaanderen</title>
      <link>/2018-04-01-ronde-van-vlaanderen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-04-01-ronde-van-vlaanderen/</guid>
      <description>Up early and a brisk walk to the train station for the first leg of our journey to Ode Kwaremont for the Tour of Flanders.
{{ more }}
All the trains where spot on and we arrived in Oudenaarde in good time for the bus to the course as we where waiting it poured down and looked set for the day but by the time we got to the Kwaremont it was dry for the rest of the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Challenge Weekend</title>
      <link>/2016-07-08-the-challenge-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-07-08-the-challenge-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Today sees the start of the final prep for the races on Sat and Sunday.
Flo&amp;rsquo;s own brand wheels
{{ more }}
Friday The challenge event is starting to feel a bit more real today as we opened registration and the vendors set up their wares. Flo and I counted the barriers at the swim and bike transition. Then when Garth was free we check out Bike course especially the turn on to and off the highway, where we will be marshalling on the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Kirkistown R2</title>
      <link>/2013-05-29-kirkistown-r2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-05-29-kirkistown-r2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2013/2013-05-29-kirkistown-r2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Kirkistown R1</title>
      <link>/2013-05-01-kirkistown-r1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2013-05-01-kirkistown-r1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/2013/2013-05-01-kirkistown-r1-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirkistown R2</title>
      <link>/2012-05-30-kirkistown-r2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2012-05-30-kirkistown-r2/</guid>
      <description>A very hard night managed to hang on for 8 place</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Da Cooley Thriller Mtb XC Marathon 2009</title>
      <link>/2009-09-21-da-cooley-thriller-mtb-xc-marathon-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2009-09-21-da-cooley-thriller-mtb-xc-marathon-2009/</guid>
      <description>Having stumbled across this event on the web, I thought I would mention it to Marty, big mistake &amp;ldquo;always wanted to do one of those&amp;rdquo; was his immediate reaction and that was it we were now fully committed. I spent the rest of the week looking for an excuse not to go but no really good one came to mind so on Friday I found myself checking over the BeOne for the adventure to follow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour of Ireland (St Patricks Hill)</title>
      <link>/2009-08-23-tour-of-ireland-st-patricks-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2009-08-23-tour-of-ireland-st-patricks-hill/</guid>
      <description>Arrive early so we went for a coffee, then panicked when we look up the hill and saw that there was already loads of people on the climb. Struggled up the hill and got a really good spot on the left about three quarters of the way up.
Writting on the Road
Waited for about an hour and where enterined by the kids having a ball writing on the road, with chalk provided by the Livestrong Foundation .</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
