<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cork on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>/tags/cork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cork on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/cork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Newtownards Part Two</title>
      <link>/2025-04-22-newtownards-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2025-04-22-newtownards-part-two/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Monday 14th April Karen was good enough to drop us of at&#xA;Enterprise to collect the hire van. Uneventful trip to Bangor with one stop for coffee and fuel&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cork Wedding</title>
      <link>/2018-03-22-cork-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-03-22-cork-wedding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This has been a strange month, severe weather for much of the Southern half of the Island and most of England, while we escaped pretty much untouched.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;{{ more }}&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have had two trips to Cork this month the first was to see Mairead and possibly cycle with John, however the weather scuppered the cycling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Called with John and Mairead on the Thursday evening (8th) with the intention of calling again on Friday, only to find Mairead  has been taken into Hospital. So Flo managed to see her on Sat and Sun before we returned home on Sun evening. Unfortunately Mairead seems much worse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cork, Family Get Together</title>
      <link>/2018-02-03-cork-family-get-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2018-02-03-cork-family-get-together/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Got Lotti into jail and on the road by 10:00 which gave us a clear run to Cork. With a Coffee and fuel stop before we hit Dublin it was plain sailing all the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;{{ more }}&#xA;We arrived in Cork around 15:30 and meet with Jane Murphy  friend of Flo&amp;rsquo;s to give her a donation to the charity she works for, naturally we did this over coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next we checked into the hotel and had dinner with Harry, Katherine, Frank and Catherine now we&amp;rsquo;re all set for tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Update and Cork</title>
      <link>/2017-02-28-monthly-update-and-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2017-02-28-monthly-update-and-cork/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not much blogging this month so this is just a catchup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;{{ more }}&#xA;Sat 4th and we meat up with the Perry&amp;rsquo;s and McCosh&amp;rsquo;s (No Children) in the Lewis Dundonald. We had been warned that there was a Loyalist Disco on at 21:00 but we where not told that as a precursor they where having a band competition so towards the end of our meal two Bands struck up a deafening racket in the small bar, sad to see that not much has really changed in the North, however the food was very good and as is to be expected the crac was mighty, we finished off the evening back at Colin and Beverly&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vets Lunch and Cork</title>
      <link>/2016-12-31-vets-lunch-and-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2016-12-31-vets-lunch-and-cork/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Flo and I went to the vets Lunch in the Esplanade, this was the first time Flo had been to one of these and I several years since I had been to one. Turned out not too bad food was good but as usual service was slow. This year the Club had laid on a comedian, heard worse.&#xA;{{ more }}&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On Friday the 9th we headed down to Cork, via a visit to Trish. The traffic was quit heavy and the weather was pretty poor but we made it in time for tea. Then the Briar Rose where we meet with John and Mairead for a couple of drinks and a chat about their up coming planes for Spain next year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
