<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spain on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/spain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spain on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/spain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Volta a la Comunitat Valenciana</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-02-08-volta-a-la-comunitat-valenciana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2019-02-08-volta-a-la-comunitat-valenciana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Up early for us and on the road for 09:00 to get to Pedralba for around 10:00 so we have time to find a good parking spot for Eddy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting off to Spain</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2018-10-30-setting-off-for-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2018-10-30-setting-off-for-spain/</guid>
      <description>Starting another adventure on, the boat to Cairnryan. Once in Scotland we will drive to Flo&amp;rsquo;s sister in London then the channel tunnel to calais and the long drive to our house in Montroi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadians On Tour</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-10-13-canadians-on-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-10-13-canadians-on-tour/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 - Lluc
Luckily Garth need his bike early and while unlocking it I noticed my rear was flat.
Got going just after 12.00 and we stayed together untill the first climb and the fragmentation began. Only one person took th van to the top. After a long stop a broken chain and one near crash when someone fell in front of Eva who escaped with a damaged tire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mallorca</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-10-07-mallorca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-10-07-mallorca/</guid>
      <description>Arrive on time even after the delay while sick person got off loaded. Picked up the hire car and just waiting for Garth and Darel to arrive.
{{ more }}
Checked in at the hotel and built our bikes. Quite impressed with the facilities and the location of the hotel. Food was good tonight.
Lluc clockwise Sun 8th
After breakfast Garth and I set for Lluc, traffic was very heavy but we soon got onto quieter roads once through Sa Pobla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Route to Cherbourg</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-28-route-to-cherbourg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-28-route-to-cherbourg/</guid>
      <description>Monday 28th Aug DAY 1 - FLIX to DAX 406 km / 252 miles {{ more }} SPANISH MAP BOOK
FLIX - LLEIDA C-12 (page 22)
LLEIDA - HUESCA A-22 (page 21 - page 13)
HUESCA -A23 - SABINANIGO - JACA N-330 - CANDANCHU / Col du Somport
(French Border) N-330 / turns into N-134 in France
FRENCH MAP - Page 203
N-134 through URDOS to OLORON SAINT MARIE [Lindt Shop]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flix - Catalunya</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-23-catalunya-flix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-23-catalunya-flix/</guid>
      <description>Can&amp;rsquo;t believe I am writing this with only 5 days of our 6 weeks left, where has the time gone, it just disappears when you are enjoying yourself.
{{ more }}
Punta De láguila 8th Aug
Flo got a walking map of the area around Asco from the tourist office. One of the walks starting at the Hermita Santa Paulina appealed to us both, so we download the gpx file to wikiloc and off we went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Vuelta a Espana</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-22-la-vuelta-a-espana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-22-la-vuelta-a-espana/</guid>
      <description>La Vuelta a Espana 22 Aug Flo liked this shoe and sock combination
{{ more }}
The King of the hills was in a place called Belltall which was about 1 1&amp;frasl;2 hours away. We arrived in plenty of time and after finding the top of the climb and a good place to park we where then able to have lunch in the town, in a Hostel Cal Feliute food was good and the service fast even though the place was packed due to the race passing through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lleida</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-01-lleida/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-08-01-lleida/</guid>
      <description>Discovered one of the pedals on BC was failing I had to swap it with the BeOne until I could get a replacement, Flo also need tubes for her MTB Lleida was the only place we could be certain to get what we needed, luckily this coincided with free entry to museums on the first Tuesday in the month,so off we went.
{{ more }}
We parked in a handy spot an first stop was the bike shop where we got all we needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Margalef </title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-07-31-margalef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-07-31-margalef/</guid>
      <description>We went for a walk to the Hermita but not before finding a bar for a coffee.
Some View
{{ more }}
The walk up to the Hermita was fairly easy, with exceptional views of the surrounding area although it was hot their was a nice cooling breeze. The walk back down was much easier as we took the road.
The Hermita
This area is known for it climbing and there where two groups doing there thing on the rocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Cycle in Taragona</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-07-17-first-cycle-in-taragona/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-07-17-first-cycle-in-taragona/</guid>
      <description>A bit windy today but decided to take the plunge and brave the C-12 to Flix wasn&amp;rsquo;t too bad.
Our First Passage On A Barca
{{ more }}
I decided on a short run due to the wind and not knowing the roads , fairly easy spin with some very poor road surface, which was made up for by a newly resurfaced section on a fast twisty decent.
On a whim I turned on to the back road into Flix and at the top of a steep hill found Flo photographing a sign, we both continued on to Flix only to find our route blocked by the river, luckily for us there was a free ferry across the river although it was one of the strangest I have come across.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Move From Altury</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-07-16-final-move-from-altury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-07-16-final-move-from-altury/</guid>
      <description>All jobs complete by 10:30 van packed off down to Bar la Rambla for a final coffee and cake. Just to wait for the new guests to arrive at 12:00 which they did spot on time and we&amp;rsquo;re off.
The Casita at the Poppy House {{ more }}
Drove for 1 hour and stopped at a Repsol for a quick bite and a drink also to let the traffic ease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping Rio Turia</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-07-01-camping-rio-turia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-07-01-camping-rio-turia/</guid>
      <description>Camping Rio Turia Day 1 Arrived 15.00 to find the place quite busy and the pool filled as promised.
Set Blu up in a nice shaded site.
Rio Tura
{{ more }}
Enjoyed a beer over looking the river and watched a pair of Swallows feeding in the roof of the bar. Walked through Bugarra just to get our bearings for tomorrow.
Camping Rio Turia Day 2 Slept late and after breakfast we walked into Bugarra for a coffee and a toastada and then beer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girona Gran Fondo</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-06-17-girona-gran-fondo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-06-17-girona-gran-fondo/</guid>
      <description>After what seemed like an eternity we arrived in Girona at 17:30 and lucky old Flo found a parking space on the river 1km from the event office, after picking up my race pack we meet with Marty for a beer and a quick catch-up we arranged to meet at 09:30 on the Pont de Pedra tomorrow.
Out in the Countryside {{ more }}
As normal when we meet the ride had changed from the shop run to a 50 mile spin to the beach with the Ards boys and some north downers .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping Pantapino</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-06-04-camping-pantapino/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-06-04-camping-pantapino/</guid>
      <description>John and Mairead are arriving this afternoon to do some work around the house while Flo and I go camping near Alarcon
Blu testing the new Tarp {{ more }}
John and I went out for a spin to Dos Aguas via La Chuffa which he hadn&amp;rsquo;t been on before, Flo Went With Amanda and was late back so it was well after 15:00 before we got on the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back in Spain</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-03-31-back_in_spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-03-31-back_in_spain/</guid>
      <description>Nearly here a week and in some ways it&amp;rsquo;s like we never left. Suttle changes here and their, a house painted, a building completed hedges replanted. One thing very obvious is how green it has become, Spain has had some unusual weather of late, snow in Murcua heavy rain in Valencia and the upside if this lots of growth. {{ more }}
All ready we have enjoyed a few spins on our bikes and hopefully many more to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mooney&#39;s and we&#39;re off to Spain</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-03-23-the-mooneys-and-were-off-to-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2017-03-23-the-mooneys-and-were-off-to-spain/</guid>
      <description>Afternoon Tea with May and Carole in the Stormont Hotel nice setting and the company was good, but the Tea left a lot to be desired I think the chief must have served his time in the ship yard.
{{ more }} The Mooney&amp;rsquo;s visited Castle Espie and we all splashed our way round the Lego Trail, with a couple of detours to climb walls fly down a zip line and get stuck in muddy puddles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roslare</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-05-01-roslare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-05-01-roslare/</guid>
      <description>Still afloat and the weather looks crap, grey and wet.
{{ more }} Flo came up with a very tentative link to knowing the Capitan so we got a trip up to the bridge where I could confirm that the weather is crap.
Arrived in Rosslare and after a short spell in the house we went to Kilmore Quay for Fish &amp;amp; Chips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherbourg</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-30-cherbourg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-30-cherbourg/</guid>
      <description>Awoke to one of the better morning on our travels to the boat lovely and bright and not so cold a nice way to start our last day on the Continent. Absorbing this before we go home.
{{ more }} Barneville - Caterat on the way we stopped in a garden center and bought a large Mailbox as you do. On in to the port we got a coffee and admired the scenery lovely spot with lots going on, all types of boats on the water or just about to be launched.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mont st Michel then on to Barneville</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-29-mont-st-michel-then-on-to-barneville/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-29-mont-st-michel-then-on-to-barneville/</guid>
      <description>Very cold last night with some heavy rain, fortunately it dried up for breakfast but it was only about 6c, on the road nice and early with our first stop Mont St Michel forecast not great but fingers crossed.
{{ more }} Mont st Michel is obviously a massive tourist attraction the car park alone is ginormous. Once parked it was nice to discover the cost also included return transport along the elevated causeway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vannes and the Vet</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-28-vannes-and-the-vet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-28-vannes-and-the-vet/</guid>
      <description>Both Flo and I spent the night running to the toilet luckily we where parked right beside the toilets and they where heated.
{{ more }} Feeling a bit off we all set off to the vet, a bit different from home only one vet no receptionist, anyway all went well and Lotti can now travel.
From the vet we walked in the center of Vannes turns out it is quite a big town, with an older pedestrian part and a more modern but much busier area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinon to Vannes</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-27-chinon-to-vannes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-27-chinon-to-vannes/</guid>
      <description>Very cold last night but got a good nights sleep in fact we got up at 9:30 so after breakfast a walk around Chinon.
{{ more }} Chinon is a lovely place with the campsite located on the banks of the Loire and one can look up to the town and once in the town you can look down over the campsite. Lotti enjoyed a trip in an elevator.
Easy drive to Vannes stopping for a coffee on the way, tonights stop is Le Conteau a large site in fact the largest so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long day on the road to Chinon</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-26-long-day-on-the-road-to-chinon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-26-long-day-on-the-road-to-chinon/</guid>
      <description>Up early this morning and on the road straight after breakfast, a bit damp so no point in hanging around. Heavy rain and heavy traffic so we diverted off the main road and took a slightly longer route but much nicer arrived in Chinon 18:30. {{ more }} Usual routine find optimum place for Blu then into Chinon for a quick look and something to eat. Found a nice Restaurant which accepted Lotti and we enjoyed a lovely meal and 1&amp;frasl;2 bottle of wine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carcassone and Castres</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-25-carcassone-and-castres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-25-carcassone-and-castres/</guid>
      <description>A quick stop in Empuriabrava to suss out Flo&amp;rsquo;s Brothers Spanish bolt hole, nice spot very built up hectic in high season. Arrived in Carcassone around lunchtime, and being in France parking was piss easy and close to the Old Town.
{{ more }} We walked around the Medevile town just what you would expect narrow streets and lots of shops although many where local crafts.
Then we followed the walking trail into the modern town and this was also very nice with a canal running through it, in the square we grabbed a spot of lunch and the back to Blu to contine on to Castres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Day in Turis</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-23-last-day-in-turis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-23-last-day-in-turis/</guid>
      <description>In to Turis for a last Coffee in Torroners, fill of fuel and back home Van packed then Bar La Rambla for the Menu del Dia. Finished cleaning and packing ready for the off tomorrow morning. {{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circuito Ricardo Tormo - Valencia</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-17-circuito-ricardo-tormo-valencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-17-circuito-ricardo-tormo-valencia/</guid>
      <description>After many years of thinking about it we finally got to the Circuito Ricardo Tormo. We had a great day, everything being free certainly helped the racing was ok with the Moto 3 and Moto 2 being the best by far. {{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Grand Easter Tour</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-02-easter-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-04-02-easter-tour/</guid>
      <description>We decided to have Easter here in Turis and travel to Cordoba on Easter Monday, when most of the Spanish traffic is heading home from Hols. This turned out to be a good decision as the volume of traffic on the other carriage way was considerable. We also had two good coffee stops which eased the trip. One stop was a place called Alacon an old fortified town over looking a river and Dam, our first coffe and cake of the trip the next stop was in a service station which was also very good with a great hunting shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falles de Valencia</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-03-16-falles-de-valencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-03-16-falles-de-valencia/</guid>
      <description>Took the Train from Bunol and connected with the Metro at Sant Isidre and arrived in Valencia, Turia to have a look at the Falles
{{ more }}
Somethings are the same the World over.
Masses of people every where, but all very good natured. Tonnes of work to produce the comic figures which will be burned on Saturday night. Many of the figures have political over tones much of which goes over our heads, but some doesn&amp;rsquo;t same problems the world over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cortes de Pallas</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-01-03-cortes-de-pallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2016-01-03-cortes-de-pallas/</guid>
      <description>Flo found this place after seeing signs by the road side last week then she looked for it on the Internet. {{ more }}
She then looked for walks on Wikiloc and found this one, sl-13. It was about 10km and very steep at the start with fabulous views, the decent was very narrow and steep one place even had a hand rail. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urrugne</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2015-12-16-urrugne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2015-12-16-urrugne/</guid>
      <description>We left Aubeterre-sur-Dronne around 09:30 after coffee and a bun a lovely bright morning for a change but much colder.
{{ more }} We arrive at Urrugne around 14:30 and quickly found the camp-site after a long but enjoyable drive. This was by far the nicest day so far with the temperature rising all the way here. Once we got settled in I showered and shaved, then we took Lotti for a walk and looked for somewhere to eat no luck in that department so we drove up to the nearest super market bought some food and enjoyed our first outdoor meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arriving in France</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2015-12-14-arriving-in-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2015-12-14-arriving-in-france/</guid>
      <description>All went well on the boat Lotti survived no problem at all. Everything was on time, the boat was nearly empty so no delays getting off.
{{ more }} We drove to Loyet and found the site no lighting, raining and the first night in Blu, got sorted reasonably well nothing to eat and nowhere open. Watched a movie on Flo&amp;rsquo;s Tablet (American Hustle)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>