<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Computing on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</title>
    <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/computing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computing on Keith&#39;s Diary and Other Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithmillar.github.io/tags/computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Symbolic Link</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-07-27-create-a-symbolic-link/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-07-27-create-a-symbolic-link/</guid>
      <description>{% highlight bash html %} ln -s [TARGET DIRECTORY OR FILE] ./[SHORTCUT] {% endhighlight %}
For example
{% highlight bash html %} ln -s /usr/local/apache/logs ./logs {% endhighlight %}
This points a symbolic link &amp;ldquo;./logs&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;/usr/local/apache/logs&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vim Indentation</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-06-23-vim-indentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-06-23-vim-indentation/</guid>
      <description>Ctrl-P toggles paste mode when in Insert mode do not include the two /
{% highlight bash html %} set pastetoggle=/ &amp;ldquo;Ctrl-P toggles paste mode when in Insert&amp;rdquo; {% endhighlight %}
{% highlight bash html %} :set paste {% endhighlight %}
{% highlight bash html %} :set nopaste {% endhighlight %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashed Flo&#39;s Phone with a CyanogenMod Rom</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-05-12-flashed-flos-phone-with-a-cyanogenmod-rom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-05-12-flashed-flos-phone-with-a-cyanogenmod-rom/</guid>
      <description>After a huge amount of fannying around Flo finally decided to to install a new rom on her HTC Wildfire, we followed the Instructions on this web site wiki.cyanogenmod.org and everything went fairly smoothly. The main reason she wanted to do this was the orignal rom was full of google apps which she didn&amp;rsquo;t use, and the phone was running out of space so she could not install Facebook, and google refuse to allow you to remove their apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copying between two Servers</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-04-29-coyping-between-two-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-04-29-coyping-between-two-servers/</guid>
      <description>Copy a file or folders between two Servers. Rsync copies folders scp files
sshfs to mount a remote dir locally
{{ more }}
{% highlight bash html linenos %} rsync -azvu &amp;ndash;rsh=&amp;lsquo;ssh -p32&amp;rsquo; basedir/ server2:destdir/ {% endhighlight %}
{% highlight bash html linenos %} scp -P32  server2:destdir/ {% endhighlight %}
{% highlight bash linenos %} sshfs @:fusermount -u mountpoint {% endhighlight %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bash Search .inputrc</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-04-24-bash-search-inputrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2013-04-24-bash-search-inputrc/</guid>
      <description>With four lines, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to type the beginning of the command (e.g. &amp;ldquo;cd&amp;rdquo;) and press the up arrow to see the most recent command containing the text you typed (e.g &amp;ldquo;cd ~/Library&amp;rdquo;).
{{ more }}
This makes it much easier to find what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for. To make this happen, create a text file called .inputrc in your home folder and put the following four lines inside:
{% highlight bash html linenos %} &amp;ldquo;\e[A&amp;rdquo;: history-search-backward &amp;ldquo;\e[B&amp;rdquo;: history-search-forward set show-all-if-ambiguous on set completion-ignore-case on {% endhighlight %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busy Sunday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-12-16-busy-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-12-16-busy-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Started off the day in the garden raking up leaves, and then we cut back the honeysuckle and found a fancy mushroom growing under the bush.
I have been hearing a strange noise from kzone, so I finally ran smartctl on it and to my horror discovered that all the drives where showing errors. I decided to replace the drive containing the OS straight away, which ment a trip to PC World for a new WD 500GB HD but coffee in Castle Espie was more inportant and being Sunday the shops hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet opened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new jekyll blog</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-12-14-new-jekyll-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-12-14-new-jekyll-blog/</guid>
      <description>Been at this all day.
{{ more }}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Spaces in File Names</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-07-22-remove-spaces-in-file-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-07-22-remove-spaces-in-file-names/</guid>
      <description>Removes spaces in file names and replaces them with
{% highlight bash html %} for file in ; do mv &amp;ldquo;$file&amp;rdquo; echo $file | sed -e &#39;s/ */-/g&#39; -e &#39;s/_-_/-/g&#39;; done {% endhighlight %} or {% highlight bash html %} find . -depth -name &amp;lsquo; *&amp;rsquo; | while IFS= read -r f ; do mv -i &amp;ldquo;$f&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;$(dirname &amp;ldquo;$f&amp;rdquo;)/$(basename &amp;ldquo;$f&amp;rdquo;|tr &amp;lsquo; &amp;rsquo; _)&amp;rdquo; ; done {% endhighlight %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The X server will not be able to send the VDPAU driver name to libvdpau</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-06-15-nvidia-vdpau/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-06-15-nvidia-vdpau/</guid>
      <description>AFAIK that is because the dri and dri2 modules from xorg-x11(mesa) opengl setup are not in path. I worked around this by
{% highlight bash html linenos %} Quote: Section &amp;ldquo;Files&amp;rdquo; ModulePath &amp;ldquo;/usr/lib/xorg/modules&amp;rdquo; ModulePath &amp;ldquo;/usr/lib/opengl/xorg-x11/extensions/&amp;rdquo; &amp;hellip; EndSection {% endhighlight %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reloading the Mutt Configuration File</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-06-11-reloading-the-mutt-configuration-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-06-11-reloading-the-mutt-configuration-file/</guid>
      <description>I find it a bit annoying that I have to re-enter my password twice every time I (re-)start mutt when I want to update my configuration file. Well, it appears I don&amp;rsquo;t need to be doing restarting mutt. The MuttWiki describes a way to re-load the configuration after mutt is running. Type the following into mutt after you&amp;rsquo;ve changed your muttrc file:  :source /path/to/your/muttrc Note that shell expansions may not work&amp;mdash;you should spell out the full path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gentoo Keyboard not working</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-05-23-gentoo-keyboard-not-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-05-23-gentoo-keyboard-not-working/</guid>
      <description>{% highlight bash html linenos %} emerge -1av $(qlist -IC x11-drivers/) {% endhighlight %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emacs Day (All Day)</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-30-emacs-day-all-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-30-emacs-day-all-day/</guid>
      <description>Started to get a feel for emacs to day, and it did take nearly all day. Finding information is not a problem finding current and relevant info can be a real challenge. How ever I did get the colour theme working and formatted the date in the calendar for European formatting. I even added the Moto GP and World Super Bike dates. Now all I have to do is put it all all together and start org mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emacs and Garth Arrives in Birmingham</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-28-emacs-and-garth-arrives-in-birmingham/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-28-emacs-and-garth-arrives-in-birmingham/</guid>
      <description>Spoke to Garth this afternoon, he was clearing out the Helena&amp;rsquo;s house in Birmingham, and had already made several trips to the dump. Sara had been round with a friend who bought the Cooker, Washing Machine and I think the Fridge. Garth already board managed a run as well. Hopefully he will be over Tuesday or Wednesday at the latest.
Started to learn EMACS today worked through the basic manual and have made more progress than in the past, so far it has been relatively straight forward (I hope).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gentoo Emerge Hell</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-26-gentoo-emerge-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-26-gentoo-emerge-hell/</guid>
      <description>As normal with Gentoo when things start to go wrong they just keep getting worse. First kdepy4 gave trouble had to downgrade sip, that sort of fixed that. Then kdepim4 wouldn&amp;rsquo;t compile, ended up leaving it, hopefully it will be fixed in the next few days. Must spend some time tidying up portage keywords etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northdowncc updates and Scripting </title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-20-northdowncc-updates-and-scripting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-20-northdowncc-updates-and-scripting/</guid>
      <description>Updated the members services section of the website today, as normal ended up doing it twice first time to prove that I did&amp;rsquo;nt like what I had and then to improve on that.
For what ever reason I thought I would try and get a script to upload this blog to fastmail using NCFTPP found a nice wee bash script then spent several hours trying to get it working, eventually success and it seemed to work well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calmer To Day</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-17-calmer-to-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-17-calmer-to-day/</guid>
      <description>Good ride with Marty today a few hills over Drumbo direction, then Daft Eddies for coffee and scones.
Helped Garth download Travel Councilers emails to his account. looks like they are going to change companys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitchen Cleaning Monday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-16-kitchen-cleaning-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-16-kitchen-cleaning-monday/</guid>
      <description>Cleaned the Kitchen today, all the units on the outside,then the floor and cooker. Saved the inside of the cupboards for another day. Managed to break the light under the cupboard.
Then I spent the afternoon trying to copy Helena&amp;rsquo;s emails etc from Outlook, waiting for the outlook.ost file to download to see if it will run on my computer.
Once again the club email is screwing with me, changed the email from address to fausto and all hell broke loose, sorted with flo&amp;rsquo;s help then the mail was unreadable in fastmail, not sure if this was just a glitch in the space time continuum or or the character encoding was wrong so I altered the encoding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Sunday</title>
      <link>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-15-easy-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithmillar.github.io/2012-01-15-easy-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Started today off with a nice cycle and of course Coffee in Mountstewart, weather for once was quite nice but cold, dry roads for the first time in what seems like weeks.
This afternoon I decided to try and install Pie Crust a web site generator,I think I have it working just need to discover how to create content. Of course before I could install Pie Crust I had to tidy up my test web sites so some where deleted, and I move Pie Crust &amp;amp; Chronicle to the virtual host directory on kzone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>